Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, let's close our eyes, everyone.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Let's close your eyes for a moment.
David S. Kong: Just…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Let's take a second to…
David S. Kong: Release whatever was going on in your…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Physical world.
David S. Kong: In your day, in your life.
David S. Kong: Just for a second, imagine.
David S. Kong: A brilliantly lit seed.
David S. Kong: Glowing… Incredible.
David S. Kong: Clarity and brightness.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: in your imaginations.
David S. Kong: And this is the image that each of your characters experiences…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As you sleep.
David S. Kong: And as you dream, not a dreamless dream.
David S. Kong: But a dream of this image.
David S. Kong: of this… Beautiful egg.
David S. Kong: That infuses you with this image of home.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And as you open your eyes, you You all… Reflect back.
David S. Kong: On what seems like another dream.
David S. Kong: You remember a vision.
David S. Kong: A way in which you… We're in a scene that
David S. Kong: Filled you with so much terror and despair.
David S. Kong: A red sky.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: a feeling of…
David S. Kong: Everything was lost.
David S. Kong: Burnt. Destroyed.
David S. Kong: And the image of a dragonette.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Lying broken.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Wings contorted.
David S. Kong: Its last gasping breaths.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: and a pool of blood.
David S. Kong: With an amber skin, amethyst skin.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you remember going into that dragonet and suddenly experiencing that dragonet's.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Last breaths.
David S. Kong: And experiencing the last moments of that dragon.
David S. Kong: But it's seeing a light hurtling towards it, and knowing that it needed to stay alive for just another moment.
David S. Kong: Just to catch the energy of this beautiful light, whatever it was.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And that as the light enveloped this dragonet.
David S. Kong: Suddenly, the dragonet felt… home.
David S. Kong: That was the image. That was the word.
David S. Kong: And I was experiencing all the ways that it ever felt home.
David S. Kong: In the arms of its best friend.
David S. Kong: Getting nuzzled and scratched under the chin.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: By a hand, by a jade hand.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: A lizard man and a kangku and a Another warrior or ranger.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then, an image of an island.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Full of its family.
David S. Kong: And hurtling through the sky.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Through the cosmos.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Through a psychedelic maze into.
David S. Kong: A clearing with a storm and then passing through that storm.
David S. Kong: and into… A poem.
David S. Kong: Where… The egg.
David S. Kong: Landed.
David S. Kong: And each of you, In a moment of inspiration, hug that egg. And as you did.
David S. Kong: Each of you experienced something profound.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: a moment.
David S. Kong: That was sacred, that none of you have ever experienced before.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zeno, you experienced…
David S. Kong: the ability to.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Both.
David S. Kong: hear and recognize tones and.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: A.
David S. Kong: type of collective.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Sound and music that you've never heard before.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The precise tuning of intervals, the ability to create something in your mind.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Symphonies that you've never heard before and symphonies that you know that if were heard by very specific entities, by a dolphin, by your mother, by the plants nearby.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That they would be in ecstasy.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Heska, you felt for, in your system, the ability to just control every single fiber of your body. The way that you were able to hunt that king crab.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Somehow, it's like you could have hung a thousand of those king crabs. You felt…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Your ability to discern any danger, your ability to strike at will at the moment that needed it was more precise than you could have ever possibly imagined.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Little Tony, you felt.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: For the first time ever.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: the ability to not only tune in to any object that you wanted, and tune the volume and the amplitude, so for once, you could be like, shut the up, and it would shut the up, or like, I wanna listen to you, and you could listen to that. Ultra-high resolution, 360 surround sound, complete control.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And also, to the extent that you play with it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You could extend that consciousness out and out.
David S. Kong: And out. And it felt like you could almost envelop the entire island, and tune into any object on the entire island. Which… was both an overwhelming and humbling, sacred experience for you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And sculpt it.
David S. Kong: Your entire life, you've.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: had this strange…
David S. Kong: Energy, this magic surging through you that you can never quite control, that would manifest in strange ways, and suddenly you'd be on the palms, suddenly you'd be near the storm.
David S. Kong: And sudden, and for the first time for you as well.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You felt an ability to.
David S. Kong: Move anywhere that you wanted, you imagined that if you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: could suddenly be in the heart of the temple, you could go there. If you wanted to travel
Audio shared by David S. Kong: To any location on the island at any moment.
David S. Kong: All of that turbulence, all of that wild energy was so calm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And so peaceful inside of you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And so, for each of you, after having this.
David S. Kong: Vision, and this experience, You sleep.
David S. Kong: You sleep.
David S. Kong: And the only image in your minds is this beautiful, Beautiful sacred egg.
David S. Kong: Even though you've encountered it just for the first time last night.
David S. Kong: Something about it is something that you've always known that has been a part of you in some deep, profound way.
David S. Kong: That symbolized home, and feels like home. And as you awake.
David S. Kong: And as the sun begins to rise.
David S. Kong: You notice that… This egg is… no longer.
David S. Kong: Glowing. It's now, it feels like whatever energy or whatever, yeah, whatever energy had been animating the egg is now, is now gone.
David S. Kong: And those feelings of great sacred power that you all felt for that period, and it felt it was it's very hard to discern time. Like you don't know how long it was that you were in that state feeling that power.
David S. Kong: But… You now… Wake up.
David S. Kong: From, rest of… Who knows how long?
David S. Kong: Back to yourself again, feeling, feeling, you know, quote unquote normal, whatever that might feel.
David S. Kong: And I'd like to begin with each of you sharing.
David S. Kong: Something about how that interaction with the egg, either the vision.
Eric Rosenbaum: Amen.
David S. Kong: This activation of sacred energy within you.
David S. Kong: How that connected with something deep inside of your, your, your character and your history.
David S. Kong: And just bring us into that.
David S. Kong: That scene.
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, Zeno's… Flat on his back.
Eric Rosenbaum: Eyes closed.
Eric Rosenbaum: Spread Eagles.
Eric Rosenbaum: In the palm of the hand.
Mike Sackton: you.
Eric Rosenbaum: with his clawed Hands over his ears.
Eric Rosenbaum: Kind of, like, twitching back and forth, and for a second, it looks almost like he's seething, but then you realize there's a…
Eric Rosenbaum: A rhythm to it, and if you knew the term.
Eric Rosenbaum: Stank face, you'd know that that's what he was experiencing.
Eric Rosenbaum: And all is silent all around, but… Inside his head, he's hearing something.
Eric Rosenbaum: That is moving him.
Eric Rosenbaum: And he sits up after a few minutes.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You know how I was thinking about starting a.
Eric Rosenbaum: Like a…
Eric Rosenbaum: a, you know, a comedy club or something. I figured it out, you guys. Now I really know.
Eric Rosenbaum: What I have to do.
Eric Rosenbaum: I gotta start.
Eric Rosenbaum: A band.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yep.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yep.
David S. Kong: you Zeno, You also, though, share with us,
David S. Kong: Something internal that you experience, like a memory.
David S. Kong: Oh, yeah, yeah. And this share doesn't have to be something your character is saying out loud. It's something that you as the player are sharing with the rest of the players.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Eric Rosenbaum: So the… auditory experience of the egg for Zeno.
Eric Rosenbaum: Unlocks for him a childhood memory he hadn't thought of.
Eric Rosenbaum: In many years, it was… A trick when he…
Eric Rosenbaum: was a young dragonetling with his family to the interior mountains.
Eric Rosenbaum: Of the circular island where they went to visit a monastery.
Eric Rosenbaum: Populated by these strange, Maybe were they flightless dragonets? They, they never flew.
Eric Rosenbaum: They were… Serious and calm.
Eric Rosenbaum: As a little one, he felt this was boring at first. He was introduced to,
Eric Rosenbaum: One of them has his uncle Kaz.
Eric Rosenbaum: And… In the evening, he was brought to a ritual that these dragonet monks were performing.
Eric Rosenbaum: And at the ritual, he heard a sound, unlike any he'd heard before, of the dragonets performing a drone.
Eric Rosenbaum: That came from deep in their bodies, a kind of choral singing.
David S. Kong: you.
Eric Rosenbaum: One that.
Eric Rosenbaum: Resonated.
Eric Rosenbaum: Every part of every dragonet, and also the building that they were inside of, playing it like an instrument.
Eric Rosenbaum: And thinking back on it, he wonders.
Eric Rosenbaum: What were they doing there?
Eric Rosenbaum: He remembers knowing…
Eric Rosenbaum: That they had a task or a project of centuries, or maybe millennia, that was nearing completion.
Eric Rosenbaum: But what was it?
Eric Rosenbaum: He counts that as one of his band's influences.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Amazing.
Tim Sackton: So Heska, has sort of… Curled up.
Tim Sackton: Maybe… you know Long a finger, sort of in a, in a nook.
Tim Sackton: Out of sight as this vision and dream is occurring.
Tim Sackton: And although he would… Never share this with anybody. He is dreaming.
Tim Sackton: A dream that… .
Tim Sackton: starts…
Tim Sackton: When he was, I guess we never really resolved what Raginet childhood was like, but they're born in clutches, right? So we're going to assume.
Tim Sackton: But as clutch mates.
Tim Sackton: Who are all much more outgoing and chatty and popular than he was.
Tim Sackton: And…
David S. Kong: I.
Tim Sackton: the… First time that he…
Tim Sackton: He was young, like a Dragonette teenager, or whatever age a Dragonette is a teenager at. I guess I should just make things up, right?
David S. Kong: Oh, yes, please, don't worry.
Tim Sackton: So he was, like, 10, which is, you know… Around the time dragonets are… Sort of…
Tim Sackton: moving out of their childhood phase into young adulthood or into sort of teenagehood, but expected to be independent, right?
Tim Sackton: Not cared for by their parents and they're, the clutches often.
Tim Sackton: You know, are relatively close to dragonets that are born in the same year.
Tim Sackton: And this, sort of, Childhood play is kind of, like.
Tim Sackton: Partly where they develop a lot of these senses about being able to infer the kind of, vibe of a competition and judge the audience and practice.
Tim Sackton: For adulthood, where they will be…
Tim Sackton: You know, involved in the, you know, participating in these, these.
Tim Sackton: Society is very audience participatory, right?
Tim Sackton: And Haska.
Tim Sackton: was trying to… You know?
Tim Sackton: Be part of the crew.
Tim Sackton: And just… He's probably thinking about this because of the earlier events of the evening.
Eric Rosenbaum: Mmm.
Tim Sackton: He thought he could dance and he he could not he could not dance.
Tim Sackton: And it wasn't even that he was bad, he was just…
Tim Sackton: boring. Like, nobody… like, he was dancing, and nobody even realized that he was performing. And in this moment of utter, like, embarrassment, it was the first time he flew almost all the way to the storm.
David S. Kong: Right.
Tim Sackton: Howard over the ocean where it was quiet.
Tim Sackton: And he is thinking now about the feeling he got from the egg, this feeling of sort of.
Tim Sackton: Not even… not even just… Sort of… it's not so much, like, precision control of your…
Tim Sackton: muscles and body as being aware of exactly where you are and exactly who can and can't see you.
Tim Sackton: And the first time he flew this far out over the ocean.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Tim Sackton: He realized that if he flew a certain way, a certain pattern over the The…
Tim Sackton: waves flashing, like, his belly at exactly the right moment. He looked like a passing cloud, and the fish below him just had no idea that there was a predator flying above them. And he just ate and ate and ate for, like.
Tim Sackton: Several hours, and came back loaded with fish.
Tim Sackton: And realized… Even though…
Tim Sackton: He continued to be quite embarrassed about everything that had happened, that maybe there were other ways to out.
Tim Sackton: exist in Dragonette society, as everyone gathered around to eat this giant load of fish she had brought back.
David S. Kong: Beautiful.
Tim Sackton: So he wakes up,
Tim Sackton: This dream having shifted to the meal quite hungry and looks over at Dino, and says…
Tim Sackton: You want to start a band?
David S. Kong: I think.
Eric Rosenbaum: yet.
Tim Sackton: Maybe a restaurant too. What do you think?
David S. Kong: No, no pause, no reply. Let's go to the next, hold, hold your, hold your reply, Eric.
David S. Kong: Xena.
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay.
Mike Sackton: So… Sculpet.
Mike Sackton: Kinda… I guess we, we just.
Tim Sackton: you.
Mike Sackton: We… it's morning, we woke up.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Sunrise.
Mike Sackton: Okay.
Mike Sackton: So… When you, when you…
Tim Sackton: Okay.
David S. Kong: It's more like 9, 10 in the morning. It's like, the sun's been up for a few hours.
Mike Sackton: Right, okay.
Mike Sackton: Whichever of the three you… for, you know, as everybody kind of awakens, you look around for a minute and notice…
Mike Sackton: them.
Mike Sackton: Sculpet doesn't seem to be there. You don't see him at first, but then he appears.
Mike Sackton: Met disappears. Met appears.
Mike Sackton: And then kinda… stretches his wings a little bit, and you…
Mike Sackton: He disappears again, and you see him from the, like, way up on the Wanderers.
Mike Sackton: Probably not quite up on the Wonder's head, because you wouldn't be able to see that far up, but, like, a fair bit up.
Mike Sackton: He's like looking down and kind of waves for a minute.
Mike Sackton: And then appears again.
Mike Sackton: Kind of along the,
Mike Sackton: And he sort of, he sort of stretches his wings and he walks out.
Mike Sackton: Towards the horizon, towards the storm, and he just looks.
Mike Sackton: calmer? Probably, the only one who would probably notice that, this would be… would be Tony, but…
Mike Sackton: Tony would have noticed over the years, you know.
Mike Sackton: He doesn't tend to go out over the ocean at all. He doesn't tend to, like…
Mike Sackton: I mean, you know, everybody fishes now and then or whatever, but he doesn't even, you would have noticed, he doesn't even really like to look out towards the storm.
Mike Sackton: from from the hand, right? He's always looking looking in towards you in the into the like the the sort of inward and he's just he's just looking out over the storm.
Mike Sackton: shakes his… shakes his wings and shakes his head and, like, slides down one of the Wanderer's fingers, after having looked out at the storm and sort of walks over. And…
Mike Sackton: Sort of smiles a little bit at everybody. He just, he looks,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Mike Sackton: Happier than, or not happier, but he looks more calm maybe than he has been in the past. And
Mike Sackton: He says…
Mike Sackton: It's not…
Mike Sackton: It's not, It's not… doesn't seem frightening anymore.
Mike Sackton: And…
Mike Sackton: thinking, and he would probably tell this story if anybody asked, actually. It's not necessarily a deep secret. It's not a story any of you would have known, but if anybody sort of…
Mike Sackton: Made encouraging noises to sort of ask what he meant by that.
Mike Sackton: He would tell a story about how.
Mike Sackton: Thanks, Tim, for inviting all of the, ages about, teenage dragonettes. When he was about 10.
Mike Sackton: His…
Mike Sackton: Clutch mates, like, he was close to some of his clutch mates, and, you know, it's not uncommon to have little… little…
Mike Sackton: competitions of daring do, right? Like, as you do in a society where everybody is
Mike Sackton: Is, you know, our performance is important and, and.
Mike Sackton: At one point, There was some… Bob.
Mike Sackton: you know.
Mike Sackton: thing out in the ocean, a floating stick or something that was really far away from shore, and the question was, well, who could go get it the first or the fastest? And Sculpit flew off, and
Mike Sackton: But, unbeknownst to him.
Mike Sackton: Or, unexpectedly, rather, the storm shifted, as it does sometimes, right? And he wasn't intending to fly near the storm, but…
Mike Sackton: All of a sudden, he found himself surrounded by thunder and lightning, and this… crashing winds and crashing waves, and… Didn't know which way was up or down, and didn't know…
Mike Sackton: Where to go, and…
Mike Sackton: He tried fighting against it for a long time, and felt like he was probably gonna die. And then…
Mike Sackton: At the end of his sort of energy, he
Mike Sackton: He… just let go, and… and… Wet.
Mike Sackton: The whatever energy was in the storm, take over and he felt something sort of move through him.
Mike Sackton: And he appeared back on the Wanderer's hand.
Mike Sackton: Apart.
Mike Sackton: You know how he got there. And from that day, he started to…
Mike Sackton: experience, that's when he started casting spells.
Mike Sackton: But he was always a little afraid.
Mike Sackton: of…
Mike Sackton: this thing that he assumes gave him the power to cast spells. It was always a little scary and…
Mike Sackton: And he was always a little bit afraid of his own magic.
Mike Sackton: And he feels less afraid now.
David S. Kong: Amazing.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): When Lil Tony was three or four years old.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He was the last of his clutch to fly.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And he wasn't, he wasn't, like, embarrassed by this or worried about it so much as he was, like, deeply annoyed that he would have to walk from place to place. He couldn't just fly there to get there.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And especially because as a small child, like, you know, as a three-year-old Dragonette.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): His favorite thing before he could fly, what dragonets like to do is to swing back and forth. They make like these little trapeze things and like swings hanging down from trees. So like before they can fly, they sort of, you know, start to get the feeling like the flying a little bit.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And he was always so annoyed because he couldn't go till he wasn't allowed to walk all the way across the island to the swing sets around the other statues.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So one day, deeply annoyed by this, and I should say that this is the point now where his vision in the egg was remembering what for a long time he thought was a dream. And now he wonders.
Eric Rosenbaum: relationship.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It wasn't a dream. It's this that happened next. So sitting in the tide pools one day at this age when he couldn't go to the other swing sets, when he couldn't fly in the littoral zone. Am I saying that right? The zone between high tide and low tide littorals. Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He's eating hermit crabs one at a time, and singing a little song, and humming his tunes to himself, like, getting, like, deep into his tunes, and then he picks up a hermit crab of enormous size, you know, maybe
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Maybe an inch and a half across.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And it's in a golden shell. And it says to him, well met, young dragon, littoral toonie.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Which he interpreted, because he didn't understand it very well, as Little Tony. And that was his name from then on. But the King of the Hermit Crabs says, I am the King of the Hermit Crabs. Spare my life, and I will grant you anything you choose. Simply cast me away.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And as you cast me away, shout your wish, and I will make it so.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And so the noun named Little Tony said, he said, okay, okay, you promise, you promise. But, you know, he's like, speech wasn't very well developed and the hermit crab, like, spoke with a thick accent.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So as he threw the hermit crab up into the air, the king of the hermit crabs and its great golden shell, he said, I wish to walk to any swing.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And the hermit crab shouted back, "So be it! Henceforth ye shall talk to any thing!
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And from that day forward.
Eric Rosenbaum: Ha ha ha.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He heard the whole world speaking to him.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And he's… he's recovered this and realized it wasn't just… it wasn't just a dream. In fact, this is the… the origin that these were gifted to him by the… the magical king of the hermit crabs.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And he feels good about that! He feels, like, more connected with his past.
David S. Kong: You know?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He never felt like a little Tony, and this… he realizes, no, I'm not a little Tony, I'm… I'm littoral and… and toony.
David S. Kong: As each of you sit with this reflection, and before you begin to share and speak with each other.
David S. Kong: You also remember.
David S. Kong: In your mind's eye.
David S. Kong: As a part of the dream that you could have sworn that the wanderer's eye was open.
David S. Kong: which It has never been open before. Ever.
David S. Kong: Was that a dream?
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
David S. Kong: And now, Zeno, your question about the restaurant.
Tim Sackton: So Heska says to little Tony, or sorry, to Xeno as he wakes up.
Tim Sackton: So you want to start a band?
Tim Sackton: Robbing us.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, man.
Tim Sackton: But what about a restaurant?
Tim Sackton: Stage…
Eric Rosenbaum: People come for the food.
Eric Rosenbaum: And they stay for the music and the carousing, you know what I'm saying?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's a whole event.
Eric Rosenbaum: Exactly.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: There's all these days that are not the Jubilee.
Eric Rosenbaum: And people just, like, hanging around, doing their thing.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hey, no, no, no, say that again.
Eric Rosenbaum: There's all these days…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, no, no.
Eric Rosenbaum: The Jubilee.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): that.
Eric Rosenbaum: People just hanging around doing their.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hanging around. Guys, what if instead of chairs at the restaurant, everybody sits on swings?
Eric Rosenbaum: You're dumb. Love it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Love it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Eric Rosenbaum: Mukhali.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And when you come in, you can just go to any of them.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's swings for everybody.
Tim Sackton: Wing.
Tim Sackton: Swing song?
Tim Sackton: There's something there, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: Needs work, needs work.
Mike Sackton: Maybe.
Mike Sackton: It needs some workshopping.
Tim Sackton: But actually I just meant I'm hungry.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh.
Eric Rosenbaum: Fair enough.
Tim Sackton: Aren't you hungry?
Eric Rosenbaum: Let's go get some breakfast.
Tim Sackton: I was… Dreaming of food all night.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, among other things, right? Oh no, you were yeah, you really were dreaming about just like eating fish.
Eric Rosenbaum: And now that you mention it, I could use some fish.
Tim Sackton: I mean… Shall we?
David S. Kong: Little Tony, do you, as a part of your, like, wake-up situation, do you actually actively go scan for… because, you know, you're in the Wanderer's Pond, do you actually scan for objects, or is this, like… how does your morning,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, does, like that moment last night where I felt like I could tune into anything anywhere, is that still in effect?
David S. Kong: No.
David S. Kong: You tried that?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, I'll try and reach out, see if I still got my…
David S. Kong: So when you reach out and you normally have like your morning routine, like when you do spend, you know, if you are you in or sculpted or hanging out at the wanderer's palm and you know you you wake up, you you you you'll because this is the this is the quiet spot, right? So you can kind of extend your consciousness out a little bit.
David S. Kong: And as you extend your consciousness out from the wanderer statue and down, even down the statue.
David S. Kong: You…
David S. Kong: You have never heard anything like this. Like, what are the five objects that you kind of near the statue that you normally would just kind of say hi to, like your kind of homies in the morning?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, usually I, I check in with Horseshoe Brad down in the tide pools.
David S. Kong: Groovy the.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Piglet, if he's on the side of the island.
David S. Kong: Yep. Closer to the Wanderer. Closer to the Wanderer.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, usually like Grandpa Jim the Cloud is usually somewhere near, sort of circles around the Wanderer and some of the trees and bushes too, just have lots of drama every day.
David S. Kong: So when you listen in, it is like…
David S. Kong: Like, all channels full, everybody, like, you can't, like, it's just non-stop, like, I cannot believe this, did you see that advertisement? It's like, it's like this crazy, crazy chatter across all channels.
David S. Kong: Like, it's a cacophony. It's like, you actually can't discern, because everyone is talking. Everyone is saying something. And it's like, I don't know if you try to tune into any one particular entity or object, but all channels, everyone is awake, everybody is talking.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Can I get, like, one… one to just talk with me and, like, tell me what's going on?
David S. Kong: Which one?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think probably like from this high maybe like Grandpa Jim the cloud
Eric Rosenbaum: like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And this is, like, this is a cloud, I have a long relationship with this cloud that goes way back, and he orbits over the island, he sees all this stuff from up above, but also he's sort of disappointed in me. Like, he has, he has really strong opinions about what I should be doing with my life.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like, wants me to go back to school, and like, it's sort of an old cloud yells at man situation.
David S. Kong: Perfect, perfect, okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm sorry.
David S. Kong: What do you do?
Eric Rosenbaum: That's what people said to me.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Thank you. So I'll wave over.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Grandpa Jim! Grandpa Jim!
David S. Kong: Tony.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What's going on? What's going on, man?
David S. Kong: Tony, you, what the hell, you've just been sleeping your day away like you always do, huh?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh my God.
David S. Kong: No, just, it's like 10 in the morning, every, the whole island is crazy right now, and you've just been sleeping in, just like you were.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Dragonette, my every need is provided for me every day, like, what do I have?
David S. Kong: Blah, blah, blah. No ambition, no goals. You're just stuck here sleeping.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Tell me, what is everybody talking about?
David S. Kong: You have slept through the craziest night and morning on this entire island. You have zero idea what is going on.
David S. Kong: How do I even begin to talk about this? It's been everywhere.
David S. Kong: These giant statues that have been here forever, these eight huge statues.
David S. Kong: Weird things are going on, their eyes are opening, there are, like, just strange, like, the mother's heart was getting warm, like, just, there's very weird, weird things happening with these statues and with the island itself.
David S. Kong: the roads, all of the eight roads, some of them are flickering on and off, there are strange lights, there are weird fountains turning on and off, there's… and there's food! There's food, just, like, appearing at certain spots, and everybody is eating, but not all the time. I mean, it is wild out there. It is…
David S. Kong: Properly crazy right now.
David S. Kong: And like I would expect from you.
David S. Kong: You're sleeping and unaware of anything that has happened.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, boy.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, boy. So I relay this information to the rest of you. What…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I don't know, what should we…
Eric Rosenbaum: spots.
Tim Sackton: I mean, I was just talking about how hungry I was. Is it good food? Grandpa Jim, what?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What's the food situation? Is it good food? Is it bad food? Is it a lot of food? Is it little food? Where's the food?
David S. Kong: Well, definitely…
Eric Rosenbaum: important.
David S. Kong: Definitely, the dragonettes are very excited about this food situation, because… and near each of the statues, it feels like there's another one down the road over here, down on the main road.
David S. Kong: there's a bunch of these spots, and everybody's getting there, and there's all kinds of commotion. I mean, I can only see so far, but it looks like some people are very, very happy with the food they're getting, some are more confused, some things… it's just chaos. This whole thing is chaos. Shut up! You shut up! He's like, you know…
David S. Kong: Somebody shut the fuck up. Anyways.
David S. Kong: The whole, the whole, everybody, everybody is just up and at them right now. : And, you know, I would, of course, expecting you to miss it and just your friends here. : I don't know what they're, they're all getting pulled into this, this thing with you and just, and the sleeping in and the no motivation thing. : That's just, it's like, it's like a curse, you know, it's like a curse how you spread it to not just you, but that low ambition to all of your friends and you're all just sleeping while all of the most amazing things are happening.
David S. Kong: But the food's just right down the road. There's definitely something happening there with food.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Okay, thank you for that part of what you had to say, Grandpa Jim.
Tim Sackton: I mean, should we go get some breakfast?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Let's get some breakfast and let's get away from this cloud, maybe?
David S. Kong: So as you, as you all, decide to head, and, and again, it's there, you know, the pilgrimage roads, they're all very, you know, everybody knows them, they all lead from the statues down, towards the, the temple.
David S. Kong: And as you head over, and you think you know what he's talking about, because they're on the roads, there are these strange, over-the-years ruins, these different types of ruins and structures that
David S. Kong: The dragonettes have decorated and used for all kinds of different things, you know, little mini playgrounds, some sites for, you know, spoken word competitions, etc.
David S. Kong: And as you travel down the pilgrimage road and fly down over the road.
David S. Kong: You get to a site which is
David S. Kong: Just a little crazy. It's one of these strange kind of contraptions that the Dragonets have seen and have always been there.
David S. Kong: But now, there's… it's alive. These are always had been ruins that had never moved, had never had any activity, and there's these basins full of
David S. Kong: Fluids and waters moving, mechanical contraptions that seem to be worrying, but, and also just like these, these bowls full of different types of foods, some that you've seen before and are very familiar with, there's some, you know, salted fish and meats.
David S. Kong: And also some, like, strange animal catch that looks really good. But then there's some really weird other food that you don't know what the it is. It's like…
David S. Kong: One of them is, like, this strange-looking, like, loafy thing that's got a texture that you don't know what it is.
David S. Kong: Some of the, the fluids and the beverages, like, have these strange tastes and flavors and, like, weird fizzy things and
David S. Kong: There's definitely stuff here that that the Dragonets seem to be very into, but then also things that are just you did no idea. I've never seen these things before. No idea. Like these weird, strange, like little individual strands and these small kind of like starchy pellets. Like it's all like a big mix of strange objects that you may or may not have identified before. And what's even crazier is in this scene.
David S. Kong: And you spot Zena also, who's here in a giant crowd. I mean, there's like probably 20 or 30 dragonets all hanging around this contraption.
Tim Sackton: Jessica immediately starts flagging the other direction.
David S. Kong: just.
Tim Sackton: Come on, guys, let's find another one.
David S. Kong: She's just in the back, she's not, you know, she's not, she's not, she hasn't noticed you. But, but, the whole scene, the whole scene is like, it's like, there's food, there's people fighting over the food, and there's people trying to operate
David S. Kong: The thing, like whatever the hell it is, they're trying to like do things and you get the sense that it's like whatever the hell is going on.
David S. Kong: It's like not really working or it's just like it's producing very inconsistent results from what everybody is hoping for. Right. It's like it's like so it's just this is the scene like as you're, you know, you're maybe like 50ft away and you're kind of, you know, you've got good vision. So you're all kind of, you know, you're spotting this.
David S. Kong: What do you all do as you as you start, as you see the scene you're flying in, this is all kind of as you're as you're as you're kind of like looking as you're getting closer.
Mike Sackton: There's a bunch of these around, right?
David S. Kong: On the pilgrimage roads, there's kind of one, you know, if the island's like a clock, you know, each pilgrimage road has like a few of these like islets where there's, you know, kind of, you know, little strange artifacts and things like this. : And this is the one that's like closest to the wanderer.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nino makes a beeline for the liquids, just searching out, like, the most interesting tasting beverage he can find.
Tim Sackton: I'm…
David S. Kong: Hold on, I just wanted to… So, Zeno, you're flying towards this whole scene.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay. Yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: Cool.
David S. Kong: What are your names?
Tim Sackton: Heska's definitely not flying towards the scene. I'm going to look for somewhere not far, not like, I don't know, 20, 30 feet away where I can hide. And then I'll just send my invisible mage hand out to sample some food and bring it back.
David S. Kong: Alright.
David S. Kong: Tony, what are you doing?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, I'll go, I'll go try some, I'm always down for some new snacks.
David S. Kong: Okay, so you're approaching and then Sculpa, what are you doing?
Mike Sackton: I'm kind of curious. I'm gonna get… so, I'm gonna summon my Unseen Servant.
Mike Sackton: And have it go co-act, like, one of each thing that it can find.
Mike Sackton: And like go bring them back to the Wanderer's Hand or something like that. Just because I want to like study this later. But then I'm going to go say hi to Zena. Like I have to say hi to her. She's like.
David S. Kong: You do, you do, you do. Xena's kind of on the periphery of the crowd, you know, she's not, like, you know, her full extrovert form. But let's come back to Xena. So wait, who's actually getting close to the apparatus? Who's, like, flying to the apparatus?
Mike Sackton: Tony.
David S. Kong: And then,
Tim Sackton: Everybody except me, I think.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay. So let's start with Tony and Zeno. So Tony and Zeno, if you're guys flying in together, are you kind of taking steps?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah, we're fine to go, yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: So, as you fly over to this contraption.
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay.
David S. Kong: And as you're getting close, you notice that the dragon that's, like… and again, there's probably, like, you know, 5 or 6 of them, like, actively, like, touching, you know, the various, like, kind of, you know, contraption elements and so on. And they're just, like, you know, you recognize one of them.
David S. Kong: Tony, like, not your clutch mate, but like a cousin, Paul, who's there, and he's just like
David S. Kong: This doesn't work. Like, none of it works. Like, earlier last night, it worked. Like, you could just think about a thing you wanna eat.
David S. Kong: And then it would just appear like it would just it would just like and you could kind of it was it was crazy like like Joey, he wanted like salted salmon and it happened and then we ate it and I was just like and then we want but then we wanted more and then it didn't do anything and it's just been the whole thing is just not it's not totally right.
David S. Kong: Like, what is it? So you hear them kind of arguing, like, about just, like.
Eric Rosenbaum: the.
David S. Kong: Like how to get the thing that they want to eat.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And.
David S. Kong: So anyway, so the two of you approach and what do you do?
Eric Rosenbaum: Tony, have you heard the term market niche?
Eric Rosenbaum: We got an opening for our restaurant here.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): things.
Eric Rosenbaum: Stop working.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Woo! I think it already stopped working.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hmm.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Wait, wait, so is it currently… is it… Paul, Paulie, what's going on? So is it… is making food, it's just making the wrong food? Like, what?
David S. Kong: It's not doing anything right now. Right now it's not doing anything. All the food from here was mostly from last night. Like.
Eric Rosenbaum: see.
David S. Kong: bunch of the.
Eric Rosenbaum: two.
David S. Kong: What's that?
Eric Rosenbaum: You would just think to it.
David S. Kong: I mean, people tried different things, I don't know, I mean, there were a lot of us here, it's hard to tell exactly what made it work, but I mean, I definitely remember, because Joey said that he wanted
David S. Kong: The salted salmon and then that definitely appeared and all of us lost it when that happened. And then we all started thinking about different foods we wanted to eat, but then it like didn't really happen again. So I don't know if it was just because it was Joey, you know, and Joey's kind of cool, you know, he's pretty cool. So maybe it's just because like the thing like Joey, I don't know what it was, but it was.
David S. Kong: He definitely made it work.
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, maybe I'll give it a try.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, give it a shot.
David S. Kong: And so, Zeno, as you approach this contraption, because again, it's…
David S. Kong: A series of these different kind of cauldrons and like, you know, chalices and bowls but then there are these strange, like
David S. Kong: You know, it's essentially mechanical aspects to them as well that just, you know, have never moved and have always been.
David S. Kong: And you notice something very strange when you get closer to the machine.
David S. Kong: You distinctly can feel it humming, like, it's…
Eric Rosenbaum: Cool.
David S. Kong: It's starting to, like, hum as you get closer to it.
Eric Rosenbaum: Right.
Eric Rosenbaum: Right, yeah… so Zeno's trying to, like.
Eric Rosenbaum: Get in the frequency with it. It's like a.
David S. Kong: Paulie, as like, as like, as it starts humming, he starts like, you know, Todd, it's like, you know, he's like looking at like, I think he's, he's starting to get a little excited. It's making a noise. It wasn't making this noise earlier.
Eric Rosenbaum: Xeno's kind of locked in.
Eric Rosenbaum: find the… Lock into the pitch, maybe harmonize a little bit.
David S. Kong: Oh, with the tone?
Eric Rosenbaum: Leon, Leon Claus. Oh yeah, oh yeah.
David S. Kong: How are you harmonizing?
Eric Rosenbaum: Beautifully, complexly.
Eric Rosenbaum: Experimenting up and down the harmonic series.
Eric Rosenbaum: Can you dig in for some subharmonics?
David S. Kong: What is, like, a music check? Like, what would you do if you're trying to do…
Tim Sackton: performance.
Mike Sackton: Performance, usually.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, do a performance check.
Eric Rosenbaum: one for me.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, 13.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: Do I so.
David S. Kong: Is that with your modifier?
Eric Rosenbaum: I have a courage knack when trying something new at a D4 as a reaction.
David S. Kong: Yeah, do it.
Tim Sackton: This seems like something new.
David S. Kong: Yeah, I'm super new. Yeah, add a D4.
Eric Rosenbaum: So that's another 2.
David S. Kong: 15?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: As he, as you start humming, like
David S. Kong: And you're doing some serious overtone, tritone shit, you know, some Jean Shinizaki shit. Like, there's kind of the bass frequency, and then you just lock into this really pleasant, just like, oh, you're kind of, you just dial in with it right above and below. Like, you're hugging the frequency it's giving you with the tones that you give it.
Eric Rosenbaum: In my mind, I'm picturing actually really delicious type of blue fish.
Eric Rosenbaum: But it's been prepared in such a way that inside of it is another slightly smaller blue fish, and inside of that one is an even smaller, delicious blue fish.
Eric Rosenbaum: Each marinated slightly differently. Okay.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, okay, okay. So the first thing that happens, the first thing that happens is, as you have that tone and you lock it in.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: Steam starts to come out of like various little fissures and holes in the whole thing and then like fluid it looks like water starts actually like moving and and and it's like it's like there's a water wheel like the mechanical like parts of it actually start to activate and then fluid starts and the dragonettes start like cheering because they're like oh my god like holy the thing is like starting to wake up it's like it's moving again it's moving again they're all they're all getting
David S. Kong: Super, super excited.
David S. Kong: So you've successfully activated the system for sure.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yes.
David S. Kong: And now you want to make a nested infinite bluefin.
David S. Kong: Neil.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's, it's a f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-ish-ish-ish, you know what I'm saying?
David S. Kong: Alright, do another person.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): There's 3 different shades of blue because it's a tritone.
Mike Sackton: Yeah?
David S. Kong: He was a chef. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's.
David S. Kong: the
David S. Kong: So Zeno, this is how it's going to work. You're going to do another performance check, okay? And the degree, however high you roll, will tell us how many fish inside of a fish.
Eric Rosenbaum: How deep the recursion goes.
David S. Kong: Yeah, how deep the recursion, like, depending on how good your role is, so let's…
Eric Rosenbaum: All right, here's the big roll.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's a nine.
David S. Kong: Not… is that with your… is it with everything else? Is that… are you adding… can you…
Eric Rosenbaum: I rolled a two plus the seven. I didn't use my knack again. And I guess a reaction I could just do again. Is that true, Tim?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: I.
Tim Sackton: So you can't spam it infinitely in combat.
David S. Kong: No, no, but in this case, but this is still something new, because now you turned it on, now you're trying to create a nested vision.
Eric Rosenbaum: I rolled a one.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 10.
David S. Kong: Okay. All right. So, okay, as you're thinking deeply about this, like, nested fish in a fish in a fish, fishing situation.
David S. Kong: There's like an output bowl at the very, very end of this whole machinery and there's all of this steam, like the very exit of this contraption, there's just like all this like kind of billowy steam covering everything.
David S. Kong: And, you know, you have an intuition that whatever you made is on the end of that thing, so you fly over, and as you look inside.
David S. Kong: Indeed.
David S. Kong: There is a large blue fin and you look, you look and it does have something inside of its mouth.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'll cut it open.
Eric Rosenbaum: I guess, like.
Mike Sackton: simple.
Eric Rosenbaum: cause.
David S. Kong: So you slice it open and you find inside.
David S. Kong: There's 1 other fish inside, it's a bluefin tuna, right, that's what you wanted?
David S. Kong: So inside, inside, there's…
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Inside there's another blue fish.
David S. Kong: Inside that other blue fish, is like…
David S. Kong: a potato. It's just not… it's not…
Eric Rosenbaum: You.
David S. Kong: You're hoping for another fish, but it's just a potato.
David S. Kong: It's not cooked and the fish aren't cooked either, so it's just like a raw fish.
Eric Rosenbaum: shout-out.
David S. Kong: Crawfish, which is, you know, I mean, you obviously dragonets enjoy enjoy, you know, sashimi. And occasionally.
Eric Rosenbaum: I think this, this is.
Eric Rosenbaum: I bring it back.
David S. Kong: All of the other Dragonets are like losing their shit. They're just like, what? What? How did that happen? How'd you do this?
Eric Rosenbaum: I bring it back to confer with my entrepreneurial team.
David S. Kong: Before you do that, Tony, what do you do when you get closer to it? As this is all unfolding with Zeno.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Amazing, Zeno. You… You… you made a… you made a fish with a fish with a potato inside!
Eric Rosenbaum: You gotta have vision, you know what I'm saying? And it's, and taste.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, that's it.
Eric Rosenbaum: I mean, this is the sort of thing.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): This is what the… this is the sort of creativity that the restaurant's gonna need, is what I'm saying, and… and I'll…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm gonna stay focused more on the swing side of things, but this is good. We have our first.
Eric Rosenbaum: right?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We have our first menu item. Fish. That's right.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's right.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): stuffed fish With potato stuffing, uncooked.
Eric Rosenbaum: yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I.
Eric Rosenbaum: there!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I guess I'll… I'll try and… I'll try and talk to the thing.
David S. Kong: You try to talk to the,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, I'm trying to talk to it. Now, like, this whole contraption thing, this has been here a long time, just not doing anything. Is that…
David S. Kong: This has been here for a long time and people like Dragonets have used it for various things. Like it's been used as like a stagecraft for like prop during like you know theater season, right? Like they would, you know, some Dragonets would claim it and use it as like a home base. Hide and seek is awesome here, you know.
David S. Kong: various times as well, like, you know, Clutchmates would, like, turn it into, like, home base for, you know, various versions of, like, Dragonite Tag, you know? Sure, sure, sure. It would symbolize all kinds of various things, but it was never, I mean, operational, like, nobody ever knew that they could move or do anything.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, so I'll, I'll try to have a conversation with it.
David S. Kong: Make an insight check.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Here comes Insight.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It is a 23!
David S. Kong: Okay.
Eric Rosenbaum: Tastes nice.
David S. Kong: What do you say?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I say… Hey, my guy! How's it going? You've been asleep forever, man! What's, what's doing? What's new?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm Little Tony.
David S. Kong: You, you don't get like a response back in words.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: But, at least right away but you get back this, like, deep sense.
David S. Kong: Of joy, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: And, you know, what it reminds you of is… it's actually reminiscent of what you just experienced. It's like waking up after having a really good sleep, and you know how, like, good you feel? Like, you kind of stretch your wings out, and you stretch your claws out, and your belly's all, like, you know, the sun's on your belly, and you're just like.
David S. Kong: That is the, the, the response that you get.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm gonna say to it, listen, buddy.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): You take your time. You enjoy this moment waking up. Some people, he looks up at the sky. Some people think you are not supposed to relish this experience. He looks up at the sky again. Some people think you're just supposed to pop awake and get doing things, but no, man.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): This sort of moment, like this is the joy of life, you gotta just sink in and experience it, right? You know what I mean?
David S. Kong: You hear a voice in your head. Oh, you mean like waking up and getting to work and doing your job and fulfilling a purpose?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh my god.
David S. Kong: You mean what this guy's doing? Which is…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): actually.
David S. Kong: Meeting the people as a part of his job? I am talking about that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Mmm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: Thank you for your service, and for doing your job.
David S. Kong: Unlike others.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Go find some moist air over the ocean.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): you.
David S. Kong: As this banter takes place, we go back to Heska, or we go back to Heska and, Sculpit. What are you guys doing? So, you're kind of watching this all unfold, this kind of commotion and a clamor, and, you know, it looks like, like, you know, whatever the, you know, something has happened, and, you know…
David S. Kong: Zeno's made some food or something. So you're kind of watching all this from afar.
David S. Kong: And what have you been doing?
David S. Kong: mean, I should ask, what have you been doing?
Tim Sackton: I've just been… Like using my invisible mage hand to just try and grab a few morsels of stuff.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Perfect.
David S. Kong: You totally do. So just the first couple of things that you grab, are you, with Mage Hand, can you like see what you're grabbing? Or are you like, what's the POV?
Tim Sackton: I mean, only if I can see it, but I'm only like 30 feet away. As long as there's like a convenient bush or something I can hide behind.
David S. Kong: Okay, but this is more like you're reaching into baskets and you know what's inside the basket, so it's a bit…
Tim Sackton: Yeah, exactly.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I don't really care, I'm just curious.
David S. Kong: So you get an assortment of things like, you know, I'm assuming you go back and forth like a couple times to grab stuff.
David S. Kong: The first time, the first time you reach and grab stuff, you get what looks like an assortment of nuts, which, you know, Dragonette, like, I feel like Dragonettes eat a little bit more like cats, like they're more kind of into meat and like, you know, it's a little less like…
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I'll try anything.
David S. Kong: So, you know, you you you however you wanna react to, like, you know, mixed nuts, but that's basically, like, the first thing you get back.
David S. Kong: The second thing that you get back, though, is actually proper, like, fish. That's, like, really fucking good. Like, this is, like, some of the tastiest, like, fish you've ever had, ever.
David S. Kong: And then the 3rd thing that you pull is like
David S. Kong: You just have never felt the texture of anything like this before. It's like long and stringy and just kind of chewy and
David S. Kong: It doesn't, it tastes pretty flavorless, honestly, to you and it's like, you just don't know what the hell this is like, like there's a kind of a strange, like, what alien foods are, is this, this machine making?
David S. Kong: energy.
Eric Rosenbaum: Got it.
Tim Sackton: I'll take some of the stringy stuff and find a dragonet with their back turned to me and just drop it on their head like hair.
David S. Kong: Make a self… make a self-track.
Tim Sackton: 26.
David S. Kong: Oh, nice. Okay, so, again, the whole crowd is here, there's a whole… Xena is here. Xena, by the way, once Xeno makes the food, is, like, beelining towards Xeno to go talk to him about the food he's making. But, but, Heska, you see, you know, this is, some, some, you know, old friends, new friends, there's, the.
Tim Sackton: I'm just looking. I'm looking for somebody who is
Tim Sackton: Who seems to be really, like, obsessed with Xena, like, staring at her.
David S. Kong: Okay, oh, they're definitely fans. Yeah, there's definitely fans. Yeah, there's definitely fans here. Yes, for sure.
David S. Kong: So you find one, and you…
Tim Sackton: Just going to drop the rose stuff on their head and then the mage hand will dip away.
David S. Kong: So… I'll go back to East.
Tim Sackton: eating fish.
David S. Kong: You do that.
David S. Kong: Yeah, and the dragonet who gets this little bit of just, you know, whatever stringy stuff on their head, like long stringy stuff, it kind of like looks around, you know, unsure like what had happened. And then it's also like, you know, like an end of like the strand like ends up like kind of near its mouth and just sort of like and starts like eating, like pulling it in. And this dragonet is sort of like…
David S. Kong: This isn't bad and like basically starts eating like the wig of like, you know, stringy stuff that's on its head and starts kind of slurping it like into his mouth and it's just sort of eating it and and the other but like then another one next to it is like watching this happen and gets a little jealous and starts like trying to like, you know, grab some of the stringy stuff off its head and then they start fighting over it so you've probably caused like a little scene now amongst like this this area of like, you know, Xena fans that.
Tim Sackton: Then I'll go back to trying to like grab some more fish.
David S. Kong: Yeah, you're, do do one more, what what what what check would this be for, it's like acrobatic? Sleight of hand? Sleight of hand.
Tim Sackton: Later hand, probably.
David S. Kong: Yeah, do a slight of hand check.
Tim Sackton: That's, 15.
David S. Kong: Okay, yeah, you're able to get some more. You're definitely able, you are now like able to, you're getting like a proper breakfast now with the food.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, that's all I really want. Cause a little chaos and get a proper breakfast.
David S. Kong: You are well on your way for that, Heska. And Sculpit, what are you doing?
Mike Sackton: So first I'm summoning my Ensign Servant and I'm gonna tell it to go collect one of everything.
David S. Kong: All right.
Mike Sackton: And then I'm gonna go over and talk to Xena.
David S. Kong: So, you know, you end up, if it's one of everything, it's like one of everything. I mean, there's like just, you know, strange dishes that you don't know, chewy, weird things that are made of textures that you've never seen before.
Mike Sackton: That's kind of cool.
David S. Kong: I learned weird sauces and stuff, it's like, I don't know, what the.
Mike Sackton: You know? Not really trying to taste it, like, I'm just curious, I'm like, I wanna study these later, right? Like, this… Especially, honestly, I'll tell it to get one of everything that it doesn't recognize.
David S. Kong: Oh, you have a lot of that, yeah, there's…
Mike Sackton: I don't want, I don't want the, like, I'm not interested in, like, the fish and the, like, and the, like, crabs.
David S. Kong: dreams.
Mike Sackton: I want the, like, weird things that I've never seen before, because I want to, like, figure out what the hell they are all made out of, and, like, whether they're edible, and, like, what they are. But not right now. This is just, like, you know, go collect this stuff while I go… while I go, you know, check in with… with…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like.
Mike Sackton: How did the, how did the voting go in the thing yesterday? I don't even remember.
Mike Sackton: Like, did she do well? She did well.
David S. Kong: Great, yeah, she recovered. I mean, after Heska's disaster.
Mike Sackton: Right, right, right, right.
David S. Kong: Moment, yeah, she recovered and nailed the landing, yeah, so…
Mike Sackton: Right.
David S. Kong: In aggregate, nobody actually really remembers what has to happen with.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: That shit happens, you know, it's fine.
David S. Kong: Tesco may, you know, hold certain feelings about it, but…
Mike Sackton: So I'll go, like, you know, like…
Mike Sackton: The show was great, you know…
David S. Kong: Wait, but just in terms of your physical locations right now, Zeno is at the, you know, with his fish in a fish. Tony, where are you in relation to the contraption?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Kind of over there next to, next to Zeno. So like at what are we sort of at like the, the one end of the contraption? Yeah.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, okay, okay.
David S. Kong: As you move over there though, Tony, just to kind of say what's up to Zeno and have a look at what he's making, you notice for sure that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: It's like humming harder, like as you get closer to the machine, like it's definitely like, like it feels like the whole system is more energized as you get closer to it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'll shout it over to the other two guys and guys. I mean, I'm good.
David S. Kong: And right now, Sculpit…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: A sculpt that also approaches.
David S. Kong: You, you, you definitely notice that the whole thing, it's like shaking now, the whole thing is kind of like moving and shaking and, and Tony, you sense in your mind, like, you know, the, the, the
David S. Kong: Kind of feeling you now sense in your, in your mind, the, the contraption, it's like talking to you per se, but you know, if you kind of tune into it, you've done it. The contraption is basically kind of like.
David S. Kong: You sense, much to the chagrin of the cloud, like a joy of work. Like it's sort of like,
David S. Kong: Like I'm fulfilling my purpose, like I get to do my thing the best that I can, like that's kind of like the, the vibe that you get and, and the cloud sensing that you are sensing something like that is now just even more like, dude.
David S. Kong: Tony, what are you doing with your life?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): you.
David S. Kong: Just like comparing you to this contraption full of purpose, serving its community, and what are you, Lil Tony, doing with your life?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We don't all have to make the same choices as each other. What's good for this thing isn't necessarily what's good for me. Anyway, shut up. Heska, get over here. Get over here.
David S. Kong: And as you get, the thing is like, it's like, and all of the Dragonets are like, like, holy shit. Like, it looks like something epic is about to happen with this system. It's just very like, it's ready. Like, whatever it is, it's ready.
David S. Kong: What do y'all do?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What if we all think of the same food at the same time?
Eric Rosenbaum: True, though.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh man, this is gonna be a problem, isn't it?
Eric Rosenbaum: laughs.
Mike Sackton: The easiest to imagine, simplest fish there is.
Tim Sackton: That's so boring.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah. I once…
Tim Sackton: I once caught this.
Tim Sackton: Fish, that was…
Mike Sackton: Scalpers.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We know you once caught this fish, Escott.
David S. Kong: Oh.
Eric Rosenbaum: That was it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, no, no, no, please, please, please. That was an insight.
Tim Sackton: It's just gonna like soak off. It was very tasty. Yeah, just.
David S. Kong: It's worth it to share.
Tim Sackton: with you.
David S. Kong: Xena, Xena, like, like, like…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh.
David S. Kong: Suddenly, suddenly emerges Heska in your pa- like, you just, like, like, like, stealth, stealth, stealth check 20, 28, and just appears in front of you and says.
David S. Kong: I want to hear the story about the fish that you caught.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh!
Tim Sackton: Heska is gonna sort of, got it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Tim Sackton: Fade off slightly and say.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Let's.
Tim Sackton: Let's all think of it.
Tim Sackton: Without describing what it was, it was really tasty.
Mike Sackton: Oh.
Tim Sackton: And then we can all eat it. Come on now.
Mike Sackton: Not gonna work.
Mike Sackton: Use your brain. So if we think of different things, won't we just confuse the machine?
Tim Sackton: It's just like looking.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Little Tony feeling chagrined has already closed his eyes and is thinking of.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): The tastiest thing you can think of, which is a fish with a potato inside, stuffed inside another fish.
David S. Kong: Okay, you're thinking wait, so Tony's thinking of a fish with a potato with a potato inside.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, stuffed in another fish. He has a real, like, recency bias here. Okay.
David S. Kong: Is it cooked or raw?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It is raw. It is in fact the fish that was just produced.
David S. Kong: Make a wisdom check.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Here we go.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's an 8 altogether.
David S. Kong: Okay, great. And then, Heska, what are you thinking about?
Tim Sackton: I'm thinking of… I'm thinking of, like,
Tim Sackton: you know, a big ahi tuna that he caught once that's, like, nearly the size of a dragonette.
Tim Sackton: Just like the, the like slice of tuna belly right from a fresh.
Tim Sackton: Caught fish.
David S. Kong: Nice. Make a wisdom check.
Tim Sackton: That is a 5.
David S. Kong: Y'all are not producing the… this is gonna be a weird output here.
Eric Rosenbaum: Brutal.
David S. Kong: What are you thinking about, Zeno? Or are you thinking of anything? Are you?
Eric Rosenbaum: Thinking about, like, the restaurant plus live performance concept. Giant cauldron of fish stew, produced in vast quantity.
Eric Rosenbaum: To please a crowd. Fish stick.
David S. Kong: Okay. Was, was Nichek?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh.
Eric Rosenbaum: Wait, so I just click on wisdom, yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: The
Eric Rosenbaum: I have advantage on this, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: Well.
David S. Kong: What'd you roll? I don't see anything.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's a three total, so it was a roll of one.
David S. Kong: You're the one.
Eric Rosenbaum: With… for a total of 3.
David S. Kong: Okay, and… Sculptor, what are you thinking of?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Ha ha.
Eric Rosenbaum: public.
Mike Sackton: He kind of looks around at the three people who completely ignored his plan.
Mike Sackton: Wow!
Mike Sackton: What's the, like, strangest thing my Unseen Servant has created… has found so far?
David S. Kong: The strangest thing?
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: This, I mean, just alien, because you just never think it, yeah, it's, it's, it's this, it's the stringy stuff, it's like, he's very, like, how would you even make that, like, how the fuck is this, it's like, super, super, like, long strands, all, like, in a thing, and then it's, like, covered in these, like, weird, like, other things, it's like, these mushy balls, and then some of them are, like, you know, that these, like, like, this, just, like, it's, it's kind of good, like, some of it has, like, some meat in it, maybe.
David S. Kong: But it's just like a… like, the stringy stuff is very strange. Like, you would have no idea, like, how…
Mike Sackton: I'm thinking of the Streggy stuff, but mixed with clams.
David S. Kong: Stringy stuff with clams. We love that.
Eric Rosenbaum: Mmm, mmm.
Mike Sackton: This is just, like, straight wisdom, not, like, any skills.
David S. Kong: Straight wisdom check.
Mike Sackton: I also rolled a one. Okay.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay.
Mike Sackton: That's free, that's free.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Mike Sackton: I.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, okay. So…
Eric Rosenbaum: The.
David S. Kong: The four of you, right? The four of you are, like, are, like, next, and everybody's so excited, because, like, nobody, like, all, all day, and all night and morning, everybody's been trying to get this, like, machine to make stuff. All of a sudden, fucking Zeno's able to make this, like, fish inside of a fish, even though there's a potato inside, it's a little weird, but everybody's eating it.
David S. Kong: And you all sit there, the machine is humming, everybody's, like, concentrating, concentrating, concentrating, you know, Hespen is thinking about this tuna, little Tony's thinking about a potato inside of a fish inside of a potato, you know, you're thinking about a fish stew.
David S. Kong: And the machine is like shaking and it's like you hear like loud giant popping noises and what starts popping out.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: are…
David S. Kong: First, the first thing that pops out is like a huge giant.
David S. Kong: It's, it's, it's basically like a cauldron.
David S. Kong: Except it's shaped like the long stringy things. So it's like, it's like a, it's like a stringy thing made out of cauldron, basically. Like, it's the first thing that comes out. And it doesn't look edible, but it just, it's just like, like, it's, it's, it's like almost like these, like, kind of weird, like, metal pipes are, like, coming out of the system. It's like the first thing that starts shooting out, and they're, like, flying out of it. It's not, like, one or two things, it's, like, projectile, like, flying out.
David S. Kong: And the dragonets are starting to dodge it because they're like, you know, what's going on with these things? And then, like, the next thing that starts coming out, it's like a potato, but inside the potato is like a small fish, like, stuffed inside the potato.
David S. Kong: These look actually kind of edible if you like the potato and those start like projectile flying out of it and it's like but it's like all of this is like machine gun style it's not like just making one it's like launching them so now it's like metal like weird cauldron strands are shooting out and then these like potatoes with little fish inside are shooting out and then and then like instead of like actual like tuna because like you'd want there to be just like
David S. Kong: really yummy actual tuna. It's like a tuna inside out. It's like a weird, it's like just the bone of a tuna on the inside.
David S. Kong: And it's like the bones of the tuna, like, randomly have clams, like, stuck on them, just like, just like on the bones with the clams, and then that is shooting out, but it's sort of like a big lump.
David S. Kong: And it's like a big giant like bone carcass with clams like stuck on it. Those the dragon ants are also kind of hopping over to and just pulling the clams off of like the bone carcasses.
David S. Kong: But this goes on for, like, a couple minutes. It's not like one thing got made, it's like this intermittent process of, like, potato with fish inside stuffed into it, weird, like, string metal cauldron things, and then, like, these bone, like, dotted with clam things, like, coming out. Chaos!
David S. Kong: And what are you all doing as this chaos is ensuing? And it stops after, like, a couple minutes, but what are you all doing while this is all going on?
Tim Sackton: I will say, well, our job is done.
David S. Kong: What's next?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Little Tony nods proudly. He's grinning. Unmitigated success, he says out loud to no one in particular.
Eric Rosenbaum: So restaurant concept wise, you guys.
Mike Sackton: Competence.
Mike Sackton: I was just shaking his head.
Eric Rosenbaum: Bye.
Tim Sackton: I think we need, like, lots of little snacks.
Mike Sackton: that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: small plates, but we don't knit off plates.
Tim Sackton: No, I don't know what that word is. What did you say?
Eric Rosenbaum: Is this like.
David S. Kong: Dragonet Tapas, or…
Eric Rosenbaum: That's what I… yeah, yeah, you know?
Eric Rosenbaum: Like.
Tim Sackton: Maybe on… the fishbone clams actually give me an idea. Maybe we serve them on… Six.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What if the theme for the restaurant is…
Tim Sackton: sticks.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Is everything…
Tim Sackton: It eats at my swings!
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Everything is reversed.
Tim Sackton: Think about it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): The bones…
Eric Rosenbaum: Sticks and swings.
Tim Sackton: No, if everything was served.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Words will never hurt me.
Tim Sackton: Then we could sit on the swings and eat them.
Eric Rosenbaum: And listen to the music.
Tim Sackton: I'm listening.
Eric Rosenbaum: Amazing.
Eric Rosenbaum: And played with sticks. So the sticks and the swings.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yep.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, this is… This is brilliant! This is…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's swing music.
Eric Rosenbaum: Swing.
Eric Rosenbaum: Music! Incredible!
David S. Kong: So as you all are debating your new restaurant concept,
David S. Kong: And this has been going on for a while now, you know? Now, you know, you've been debating and discussing, and the whole kind of dragonette clamor, you know, of this contraption.
David S. Kong: But then also just your presence and somehow your presence activating the machine and making more stuff happen.
David S. Kong: As you're all kind of enjoying this moment, and everybody's enjoying it.
David S. Kong: You see, coming up down the road, flying down the road.
David S. Kong: a couple of dragonets who are, dressed in, ceremonial garb that you recognize from, the festival the day before. And this… there are a few dragonets that, are part of this larger.
David S. Kong: you know, kind of shamanic sect of dragonets. As you'll recall from the opening of the festival, where each of the, each of the various, community… dragonet communities associated with each one of the statues, had an elder come And…
David S. Kong: As you all are kind of hanging out, a couple of these dragonets wearing some of the more ceremonial garb, they pop by, and they're all kind of talking to each other, and a couple other dragonets, like, talk to each other, and they're all pointing at you. They're pointing at the four of you, basically.
David S. Kong: And the dragonettes wearing the more ceremonial outfits, they kind of fly over and land.
David S. Kong: And they say,
David S. Kong: One of them in particular, he's got, you know, some face paint on and, you know, he's wearing a cloak, and he's looking at you all and he's like.
David S. Kong: Did you turn this machine on?
Tim Sackton: No.
Mike Sackton: Not on purpose.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No.
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe a little.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Kinda.
David S. Kong: How did you…
Eric Rosenbaum: I mean, it was… it was skill, really.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It was.
David S. Kong: What?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: skill.
Eric Rosenbaum: Really?
Mike Sackton: Yale.
Tim Sackton: Well, there was a lot of tuna.
Tim Sackton: And some clams involved.
David S. Kong: The dragonet, he's looking, you know, and he looks at y'all and says, I'm Ilse.
David S. Kong: I work with Shaman Oru. Shaman Oru is like the head elder from the ceremony. We have been trying to figure out what the hell is going on in the island since last night.
David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: This machine was making all kinds of stuff last night, and then we got reports that… and just hearing now that it was turned back on, and you all have been able to
David S. Kong: Use it.
David S. Kong: What did you do to make it do all this? : And he's kind of looking at like both the like actual food and then also like what the fuck are all these weird like, you know, just the outputs of your.
Tim Sackton: Hasca's just kind of kind of nodding and looks over at Sculpet and says he can explain it all.
David S. Kong: Ilse looks at Sculpit expectantly.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Mike Sackton: Explain, wow.
Mike Sackton: The.
Mike Sackton: Hmm.
David S. Kong: Let's, I think Shaman Uru, you should speak with Shaman Uru about this. He will want to know that.
David S. Kong: this is happening.
David S. Kong: I think this will be good, because maybe you can make more food for everybody.
Mike Sackton: Peter?
Mike Sackton: Sculpa kind of points at the cauldron.
Mike Sackton: Why I got the grid?
Mike Sackton: The food is a bit… Of a work in progress.
David S. Kong: But the.
Mike Sackton: Work last night.
Mike Sackton: Did people just walk up to it and it worked?
David S. Kong: The stories that we heard first , it just was making things on its own. And then. But it didn't last long. It was just if you happen to be near one of them. I mean , there's , you know , there's all around the island , these weird things. I mean , we never knew that they did anything.
David S. Kong: But…
Tim Sackton: I'm just gonna lean over to Dina and I'm gonna whisper.
Tim Sackton: Isn't this gonna cut into our market for our restaurant? Do we actually want them to work?
Eric Rosenbaum: We can get some kind of exclusive licensing agreement.
Mike Sackton: Now.
David S. Kong: laughing.
Mike Sackton: Guys, don't worry!
Mike Sackton: People like going to restaurants for the music.
Eric Rosenbaum: Franchising.
David S. Kong: Ilsa, like, y'all are, like, in a huddle, like, discussing this, and then Ilsa's head, like, appears into the huddle, and he's like.
David S. Kong: Wait.
David S. Kong: If you're starting a restaurant business, can I help?
Mike Sackton: Do.
Eric Rosenbaum: Now, here's the thing.
Mike Sackton: These guys need advice.
David S. Kong: I have all kinds of advice, yeah.
Mike Sackton: Maybe, like, for, like, for, like… for, like, one…
Mike Sackton: Meal a week, you could give some good advice to them.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I.
David S. Kong: mean.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Could you preview like two pieces of advice for us right now so that we know the quality of like the kind of advice that we should expect?
Eric Rosenbaum: guys.
Eric Rosenbaum: Our new restaurant has a community vibe.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Mmm.
Eric Rosenbaum: Very welcoming, collaborative.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, of course.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Brooks.
Eric Rosenbaum: So.
Tim Sackton: No!
Eric Rosenbaum: It's a work in progress, but…
Mike Sackton: They need some advice.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Mike Sackton: Sculpt it, we'll say.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Tim Sackton: No, it's where we… it's where musical acts come to be discovered. We have to let people in.
David S. Kong: Wait, but just in my… That's what makes it so… If you're asking for advice, just, you know, consider me as a part of this.
David S. Kong: And he has this, like, shamanic cloak that he just kind of, like, takes, and, like, he takes off the cloak and flips it inside, so it's like, now, like, all of the cool, ornate stuff is just, like, flipped inside out, and now he's just, like, wearing, you know, he just flips it, turns it back on. Okay.
David S. Kong: This is what I think we should do.
David S. Kong: You know how you have the clams?
David S. Kong: on the fish bones.
Mike Sackton: We don't know how that happens.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: But that's a vibe.
David S. Kong: That's a vibe. I think presentation-wise.
Tim Sackton: That was my idea. We already had that idea. Food on sticks.
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay.
David S. Kong: Food-on-the.
Eric Rosenbaum: I heard him, I heard him, yep.
David S. Kong: I love it, but I love it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): or.
David S. Kong: What I'm saying is, you can do all kinds of other things. You could have, you know, you could have pig, you could have, you know, whatever food you want, and then put and decorate it.
David S. Kong: With the bones, right?
David S. Kong: What do you guys think?
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't know about Bones decoration, but the.
David S. Kong: No, the bones and then you stick. Yeah, I'm agreeing with the sticks idea.
Eric Rosenbaum: This we're sticking with sticks. Yeah. And.
David S. Kong: And here's… here's… wait, wait, wait, and just my other, my other thing. You know, like, I don't know, and he picks up one of, like, the iron, like, it's like a cauldron material, like.
David S. Kong: He's like, this is my idea around these things.
David S. Kong: We don't give these to anybody.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Ha ha ha ha.
David S. Kong: You guys, I know you made a lot of them, like it was a good idea, but I think.
Eric Rosenbaum: You can make frames out of it.
David S. Kong: I think this is… I think this is a… What?
Tim Sackton: Yeah, what do you think we're gonna make our swings out of?
David S. Kong: These?
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
Mike Sackton: They don't really have a good aesthetic here.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): A little different, different vision for the swings.
David S. Kong: As you all are continuing this conversation, the other… another, like, shamanic, dragonet guy comes over and is, like, like, staring, like, like, at Ilsa, just like, dude, what the is there? Where, like… and he's, like, pointing at the cloak thing, and he's like… and then Ilsa's like, oh, oh oh oh and then he's like.
David S. Kong: That's my supervisor. And then he goes and he flips flips the thing back on again, and now he's got his, like, shamanic garb on, and he's and he looks and he says.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
David S. Kong: Yeah, Shaman Uru, he would like to, speak with you, the four of you. Yeah.
David S. Kong: Yeah, and he's kind of looking up at the guy, and he's like, yeah, he… See my boss.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, of course, I'll, deep respect for Shaman. Should we bring, should we bring this stuff with us?
David S. Kong: I think we bring at least some of everything.
David S. Kong: That's a good idea.
Tim Sackton: we.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Even… even the cartridge?
David S. Kong: I think a little bit of everything is…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): the.
David S. Kong: Good situation.
Tim Sackton: Can someone go find some sticks? I mean, we got to stick to our concept, right?
David S. Kong: You can spend a few minutes and collect some sticks. You can definitely do that for sure.
Eric Rosenbaum: Or like the fish ribs.
Eric Rosenbaum: We can use those.
David S. Kong: You spend you spend the next like and the and basically everybody kind of helps because once they realize that shaman Uru is you're being summoned to go see the shaman, everybody else is kind of like helping you like collect the right sticks, putting like various foods on the sticks. It's kind of cool because it's almost like the restaurant concept is a bit coming to life before your eyes. Like you're kind of seeing different bone carcasses being decorated with different foods, but also like some of the weird foods that you don't recognize.
David S. Kong: The whole thing is like very avant-garde and like, you know, I don't know if Scott.
Eric Rosenbaum: business.
David S. Kong: Your thing, but sculpt it. You kind of feel like there's a new artistic boundary that's being pushed that you have never seen.
Eric Rosenbaum: Boom.
David S. Kong: Like both the foods are interesting, like the foods themselves being different is interesting, but now the combination with the weird decoration and you're sensing like a moment here in Dragonet food art history.
David S. Kong: And it's a cultural moment that makes, like, the small little hairs on your fur
David S. Kong: You know, kind of stand up a little bit as you're watching this.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hmm.
David S. Kong: Do you have any other reaction, Sculpet, to this moment that's unfolding in Dragonite history?
Mike Sackton: It, I think there's something here, guys.
Mike Sackton: you…
Eric Rosenbaum: That's what that's what.
Eric Rosenbaum: You're starting to see the vision!
Mike Sackton: It… It's almost there! You're so close, like, this…
Eric Rosenbaum: Well, there's, there's one more.
Mike Sackton: Well, I think you need some… See.
Mike Sackton: See, taste… Is both the ideas and knowing which ideas not to do.
David S. Kong: No, it tastes just like snacky snacks.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: I'm with him. I'm with, like…
Mike Sackton: You're so close to brilliance, guys. You're, like, 4 feet.
Mike Sackton: From Brilliance, and there's a cliff, and you're about to walk from Brilliance off the cliff.
Tim Sackton: I like clefts.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's like that.
David S. Kong: Part of the island where you can get.
Mike Sackton: He just, like, puts his wigs over his head.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Maybe he's talking about that restaurant called the Cliff. Do you know?
David S. Kong: I thought, no, but Tony, don't you remember? I think that there is that restaurant called The Brilliance that has really good clams.
Tim Sackton: Wait, no, I thought we invented the concept of restaurants.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: accept.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): if… Huh.
David S. Kong: Anyways, this whole con- yeah, so this conversation continues as the collection of the food happens, and then eventually, after quite some time, you sort out, get all the stuff, and, you move with the two, shamanic.
David S. Kong: Dragonettes and make your way, towards the temple.
David S. Kong: And as you head over.
David S. Kong: And enter a tent that's near the periphery of the grounds from the Jubilee the day earlier.
David S. Kong: you… Enter, one of the tents, and… Sitting there… is, shalom.
David S. Kong: Who is an old dragonette.
David S. Kong: Old, old, old. It's hard to know in,
Mike Sackton: Ugh.
David S. Kong: Dragonet, human years, how old exactly he is, but, he's the oldest Dragonet anybody has ever seen or heard of.
David S. Kong: And he he welcomes you all into his tent.
David S. Kong: And
David S. Kong: every… all of you know him, like, at various points in your Dragonette childhood. Like, there's, like, a version of, like, Dragonette Sunday School happens, where, like, the drag… like, the drag… like, basically the shamanic Dragonette elders, like, they try to, like, you know, kind of teach you stuff about, like, the importance of clutches, and why it's important to have, you know, your family, and why, you know, kind of certain aspects of just these traditions around Dragonettes that, you know, like.
David S. Kong: La la la, like, you gotta do this, you gotta do that.
David S. Kong: So you've definitely, like, been in his presence before, and certainly the other shamanic dragonets revere him, and he, oh, and partially, but just because he has, like, the coolest moment of the festival every year, he basically gets to collect all the objects from the other dragonets, and then, you know, kind of kicks off the festival. Everybody knows him, but he's also… each of you, at some point in your lives, have had at least one
David S. Kong: you know, just positive moment with him. Either, you know, he kind of picked you up when you were having a hard time, gave you a little hunting tip, you know, Tony, for you, like, made you feel okay about not necessarily having, like, you know, a deep mission or purpose, you know, in contrast to those fucking clouds.
David S. Kong: So, you know, he's been a very understanding figure in the larger Dragonet community, and he welcomes, you know, he gives each of you kind of a little wing hug, and then welcomes you in.
David S. Kong: And as you sit down in his tent, he looks at each of you and says.
David S. Kong: I've heard some strange stories since last night.
David S. Kong: Well, first of all, strange things have been happening all over the island. I'm guessing you've heard by now, but the roads have been lighting up, these machines have been working, the fountains have been turning on. People say that the eyes of the statues have been opening and closing. There is some…
David S. Kong: Something happening on this island that.
David S. Kong: Is very Exciting. And new, and we haven't seen or heard anything like this.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And.
David S. Kong: memory.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: The 4 of you here, I, we, we heard that you were able to turn 1 of the machines on. What did you do to turn the machines on?
Mike Sackton: We walked near it.
Mike Sackton: Didn't they all?
Eric Rosenbaum: How to kind of… I had a kind of deep humming to it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): then.
Eric Rosenbaum: The.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): closer we got, like the louder it got and then we thought really hard.
David S. Kong: them and you.
Eric Rosenbaum: I sang a little bit. I sang a little bit as well.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, we could try.
Eric Rosenbaum: Something delicious and.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Exactly, and then it comes out backwards.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like I thought about a fish that was stuffed with another fish that was stuffed with a potato, but what came out was a potato that was stuffed with a fish. So what I should have done was think of a potato that was stuffed with a fish.
David S. Kong: Did you do that? Did you think about the potato with the?
Eric Rosenbaum: Good idea.
David S. Kong: with the fish.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, we didn't try that. We, you know… You should try that.
David S. Kong: Later.
Eric Rosenbaum: Good idea.
David S. Kong: You should try that later. But wait!
David S. Kong: But…
David S. Kong: I still don't understand what did you do you said you sang to the machine and it turned on.
Eric Rosenbaum: I think… I think I was resonating with it.
Eric Rosenbaum: I think.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's kind of like a new thing I'm experimenting with, like, bye, Bing.
Eric Rosenbaum: With, musically with, you know.
Eric Rosenbaum: Other drone knits, weird machines… It's just this new idea I've got.
David S. Kong: The shaman like kind of lights up, it's like
David S. Kong: Wait here. I'm gonna go get some things.
David S. Kong: And he goes back into this, like, back room, and it's like… and you're hearing all kinds of crazy noise, because, like, inside the space, by the way, too, there's just all kinds of strange artifacts, shiny things. If you think about, like, the, the found competition of just, like, cool, shiny, weird things, like, this room has just got all kinds of stuff. Not necessarily decorated with a great interior design, it's a bit kind of like a hoarder, but…
David S. Kong: It's fine.
David S. Kong: But he goes back, and he digs out, and then he finds, and he comes back with
David S. Kong: This circular object, and, you know, for a dragonet claw, it's probably, like, this size.
David S. Kong: Relative to it. And it's weird, because it's a perfect circle, and you don't really see objects that look like perfect circles, and it's made out of this…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You know, kind of hard, shiny material.
David S. Kong: And when you look at it, you know, he kind of is holding it in 2 claws and there's all kind, there's basically kind of like structures inside these very tiny little components and then, you know, kind of like, what looks like a, like a spinning wheel, like inside.
David S. Kong: And he's holding it.
Eric Rosenbaum: Whoa!
David S. Kong: And he's like, Look at this.
David S. Kong: We've had these… I have a few other like this.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And last night, It started to click.
David S. Kong: It's crazy because it's clicking again.
David S. Kong: And he's looking at it, and you can hear, like, a.
Eric Rosenbaum: Zeno, like, gets his face right up to it.
David S. Kong: As you get closer to it, Zeno.
David S. Kong: The clicking gets louder, and it's, like, it…
David S. Kong: You're looking at it and there's basically all of these kind of circular structures with these little kind of like fish fishy teeth that are all grinding and you've never seen anything like it. Like it's like the grinding of one circle impacts the grinding of another circle and then there are these other circles.
Eric Rosenbaum: well.
David S. Kong: all, like, moving… I mean, it's just… it's… it feels like magic, except it's not, like, magic in the sense that you've ever seen it, but it's just, like, somebody built something, and you have no idea how anyone could possibly make something like this. I mean, it's just… you've never seen a contraption like this before in your entire life.
David S. Kong: But it's definitely moving, and it's definitely alive.
Eric Rosenbaum: Can I have this? This is amazing. What is this? Where did you find this thing?
David S. Kong: We found it in the temple. There are things like this all over the island. We've, over the years, I mean, back there, there's all kinds of, I mean, each of the shamans, we all have a, you know, everybody brings us some of these weird things that we don't totally know what we're doing, but I've got a whole bunch of them, and last night they all started turning on.
Eric Rosenbaum: It was never ticking before.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: No, no, never.
David S. Kong: They would never tick.
David S. Kong: They were never ticking.
Eric Rosenbaum: What do you think it does?
David S. Kong: And now, now here with you.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm just taking…
David S. Kong: sticking again.
David S. Kong: And the shaman, he pauses and just has this kind of like Deep pause, and look.
David S. Kong: What?
David S. Kong: Has anything strange happened to you?
David S. Kong: The four of you, recently?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Let me define strange.
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm sorry.
Mike Sackton: You know what he's talking about.
David S. Kong: I actually don't know what I'm… I'm just… I'm just curious, because you four… When you're… around…
David S. Kong: The food machine makes the food, these boxes, these, these kind of spirit things start making noise, like
David S. Kong: What's going… like, what is it… what are you…
David S. Kong: Is it the singing? Is it the, what's, you know, what's going on here?
Mike Sackton: I mean… There, there was the… Big egg that…
Eric Rosenbaum: There was It's a good point. There was the whole thing about the egg.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, maybe.
Tim Sackton: Maybe we should.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): And had a magical vision.
Tim Sackton: The egg and the.
David S. Kong: which.
Tim Sackton: Food machine.
David S. Kong: Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh.
Mike Sackton: the.
David S. Kong: The shaman's like.
David S. Kong: Go back to the egg again. What What are you talking about with an egg?
Mike Sackton: Subscribe! I mean, you've seen eggs.
David S. Kong: You all came from eggs. I was there when you were all hatchlings. Yeah.
Tim Sackton: But this is a lot bigger.
Mike Sackton: Like, you know, Sculpet, like, jumps up 7 feet, like…
David S. Kong: And what? And then what happened? Where was the egg?
Mike Sackton: In the Wanderer's Palm.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: There was an egg in the wanderer's palm.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: When, when was this?
Mike Sackton: Last night?
Tim Sackton: last night.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's, you know, pretty much…
David S. Kong: Wait, last night there was an egg in the Wanderer's palm.
David S. Kong: And then…
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, you do, yeah.
David S. Kong: And then, what did you do with the egg?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I mean, we.
Eric Rosenbaum: Ahem.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We hugged it, but it makes you wonder a little bit.
David S. Kong: Wait, wait, wait.
Mike Sackton: Probably.
David S. Kong: the.
Mike Sackton: The air was.
David S. Kong: Wanderer's palm, and then you hug the egg.
David S. Kong: Why did you hug the egg?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Do you know, like, when you see someone, and you're just like, they need a hug, right? Like, you just, you get a vibe from a person, and you're like, oh, buddy, I got you, right?
David S. Kong: Okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think it's pretty straightforward.
David S. Kong: You hugged the egg?
David S. Kong: That was in the Wanderer's Palm. How do you get there?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, I hypothesize it was an enormous dragonet mom who climbed all the way up and then just flipped out the egg.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): But we have no evidence for that.
David S. Kong: Yeah, I don't think that happened.
Mike Sackton: Magic, probably.
David S. Kong: What kind of magic?
Mike Sackton: There's kinds of magic?
David S. Kong: I said, what kind of magic would, I've never heard of, I mean, I'm, I'm, I'm kind of the, you know, old wise shaman guy here and I, I don't know of any magic that would create a giant egg.
David S. Kong: And put it in the wall.
Tim Sackton: Oh, well, it's easy to create a giant egg. Oh, you mean a real giant egg?
David S. Kong: Isn't that what you're talking about?
Mike Sackton: Yes.
Tim Sackton: Yes.
David S. Kong: So…
Tim Sackton: Can create a giant egg though.
David S. Kong: Did the egg hatch?
Tim Sackton: No.
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't think so, no.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Was it simple?
Eric Rosenbaum: load though.
Tim Sackton: do…
David S. Kong: You tell me, you're the ones that hugged the egg. Why did you, and you hugged the egg just because of vibes?
Mike Sackton: Little Tony, I think, was pretty clear about why we have the egg.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: And then what happened after you hugged the egg?
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Mike Sackton: when.
Tim Sackton: I mean, it was morning and we were hungry and we went to find some breakfast.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What about… what about… Well, like, we…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We kind of tripped for a little bit before then though, right?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I mean, if we're being honest.
Eric Rosenbaum: That did happen a little bit.
David S. Kong: What is that? What is that?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Just a little trip through time and space.
David S. Kong: what.
Eric Rosenbaum: Right.
David S. Kong: You trip through time and space. What?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, the wounded guy.
Tim Sackton: It's like a weird dream.
Tim Sackton: You know, sometimes when you, like, eat something that…
Tim Sackton: Doesn't really sit right in your stomach and you go to sleep and then.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Mushrooms he's talking about.
Tim Sackton: you.
Mike Sackton: I think he's talking about, like.
Mike Sackton: The seventh fish when you should have only had five.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Mmm…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Or, like…
Tim Sackton: Sometimes you just scoop something up from the bottom.
Eric Rosenbaum: the ocean.
Tim Sackton: allow.
Eric Rosenbaum: All right.
Mike Sackton: Like, strange shellfish, weird, you know.
Mike Sackton: There's those squiggly worm things that you're not supposed to eat, he probably eats them.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What was the question?
Mike Sackton: Why do you eat the weird squiggly worms you're not supposed to eat?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I mean, it's an adventure, right?
David S. Kong: Let's just back up.
Tim Sackton: Do you sometimes like to have weird dreams? Come on.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, okay, wait, but the traveling through space and time thing, what happened again? Wait, you traveled through space and time after you hugged the egg.
Tim Sackton: Well, it was a dream.
David S. Kong: You had a dream, but wait, you all had the same dream?
Mike Sackton: Did we?
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, And there was a, there was a guy who was, Bleeding.
David S. Kong: There was a.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hopu is okay.
David S. Kong: A bleeding guy, okay.
David S. Kong: In the, in the dream, you all saw the bleeding guy?
Tim Sackton: Unlike the red sky.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh yeah.
David S. Kong: Red Sky.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): See ya.
David S. Kong: Yeah, happy Scott.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, oh, oh, oh. And then…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): you.
Eric Rosenbaum: And then coming home, something about home too, definitely.
Tim Sackton: Not… not a happy red sky.
David S. Kong: Oh, like a, like a, today's a fun day.
David S. Kong: Red Sky.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I would even, this may be a little extreme, but I would even say like an unhappy Red Sky.
David S. Kong: It was an unhappy red sky.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, it seemed pretty unhappy, but…
Tim Sackton: Like… sorry, what was the question again?
David S. Kong: I'm just trying to piece together, you hugged the egg and had a dream about a bloody dead guy, and then there was a.
Tim Sackton: And a red sky and home. And then we woke up and we went to get some breakfast because.
Tim Sackton: That's what you do when you wake up after a strange night and.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It was…
Tim Sackton: Now we're here.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): depressing oh my God it was so depressing.
Mike Sackton: Wait, which part?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): The dream, right?
Eric Rosenbaum: you No, no, no.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): The breakfast was great.
Mike Sackton: Oh, sorry, I thought you meant breakfast.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh, no, no, no, no.
Mike Sackton: I can go.
Eric Rosenbaum: For another breakfast.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: actually.
Tim Sackton: Do you have more food?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Shaman, do you have breakfast actually, though?
David S. Kong: which.
Eric Rosenbaum: Is it lunchtime? I could go for some lunch.
David S. Kong: Younglings, younglings, a moment, a moment, a moment.
David S. Kong: Strange things are happening on this island!
David S. Kong: You all are mixed with this whole thing somehow. There was an egg that appeared, you hugged it, you had a psychedelic dream, and there was a dead guy, and then a blood sky, and then you woke up and had breakfast with a food machine that's never been turned on.
David S. Kong: This is all… Awesome. It's just…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): listen.
David S. Kong: Great day, isn't it? What an awesome day is this.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): The dead guy was a purple guy. Like it was an old dead purple guy with like silver fur and like purple scales.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Do you know him?
Eric Rosenbaum: Old guy, definitely an old guy, yeah.
David S. Kong: Old guy, old dead guy with purple scales.
Eric Rosenbaum: Maybe not dead.
David S. Kong: Interesting question.
Eric Rosenbaum: dying?
David S. Kong: I mean, there's definitely, you know, purple. It's not, not many of us are purple.
David S. Kong: So, that is interesting.
Mike Sackton: I want to go back to the, like, didn't all the machines turn on last night?
David S. Kong: They did. Yeah.
David S. Kong: But just for a little bit, and then they turn back off again.
David S. Kong: And then they've just been kind of turning on and off a little bit here and there.
Mike Sackton: When do they?
Eric Rosenbaum: Totally.
Mike Sackton: Wait, we're not the only ones to make the turn on?
David S. Kong: Oh, yeah, I think you're the only ones that are turning them on, but they all turn… okay, timeline, because apparently you all missed this.
David S. Kong: Last night… After the main performances were over.
David S. Kong: Not sure exactly what time it was, but it was getting late.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: There was a moment.
David S. Kong: There was a moment that was everybody, we got reports across the island all at once, there was a single moment.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Where…
David S. Kong: Somebody said the wanderer's eyes turned on. Somebody said that Sybil's had a third eye appear.
David S. Kong: Strange things started happening.
David S. Kong: The Warlords…
David S. Kong: Axe started to, I mean, it was like, I mean, I think that they were hallucinating potentially. I don't know, but.
Tim Sackton: the…
Tim Sackton: Did you look into what they were serving at the festival? Are you sure there wasn't some bad mushrooms in there?
David S. Kong: I mean, it's a great question, but I think we have had enough independent reports now, and the food machines, guys, the food machines. I mean, there's machines on the island just making food.
Mike Sackton: But this was when the egg was in the Wanderer's palm, right? We all know that, right?
David S. Kong: And you know, I haven't seen this egg. You're the ones that have seen the egg.
Mike Sackton: It must have been, right? Like, when did this happen?
David S. Kong: Last night.
Mike Sackton: Like.
Tim Sackton: Oh.
Mike Sackton: But like late-ish right. Yeah, late-ish Maybe.
Tim Sackton: Maybe if we can get another egg?
Tim Sackton: It could power our restaurant.
Eric Rosenbaum: Now you're talking.
David S. Kong: Okay, I'm very intrigued. I was a restaurateur earlier in my career before I was a shamash. I wanted to stop.
Mike Sackton: wait.
David S. Kong: I want to discuss this with all of you because we could have a hit with these machines.
David S. Kong: But before we go down that path, I have a solemn duty. And then he was like starting to like flip on his own shamanic. And then he was just like, wait, wait, wait. No, no, wait. He's like, he's like, I don't know.
Eric Rosenbaum: the.
Mike Sackton: Wait, hold on, hold on.
David S. Kong: I know.
Mike Sackton: You have a solemn duty, it's like really important for all of us to follow the solemn duty, but.
David S. Kong: I mean, not really, but go ahead.
Mike Sackton: But but.
Eric Rosenbaum: the.
Mike Sackton: Well.
Eric Rosenbaum: sculpt.
Mike Sackton: it was only like 20% non-sarcastic at that sentence. But like, they really need some advice. They're so close to inventing like a new art form.
Mike Sackton: But they're so distractible.
Mike Sackton: Like.
David S. Kong: The shot, or, or, or, like, like, like has a real, like, kind of looks over at Sculpit and it's like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Sculpt it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you have.
David S. Kong: gift.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Them?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They like gifts.
David S. Kong: We all like gifts. We all love gifts.
Tim Sackton: No, we haven't, Jeff.
Mike Sackton: Oh.
David S. Kong: I love gifts.
David S. Kong: And you have one.
David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: I do love restaurants, I will say that. I love restaurants. So I'm super happy, after we finish the other conversation about the island, you know, waking up and all the weird… because, like, let's… and as you're all, like, kind of still continuing in this whole back and forth.
David S. Kong: More dragonets burst into the room.
David S. Kong: And one of them you recognize is Rosca.
David S. Kong: Except Rob.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, no.
David S. Kong: Kind of got his, he's actually, he's still wearing that, his same festival garb. And they all come in and then they say.
David S. Kong: The Wanderer's Eye. It's open again. We should go check it out.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, probably.
Mike Sackton: What color?
Eric Rosenbaum: Let's go see.
David S. Kong: It's that we just got, we just got the report that's happened.
Mike Sackton: The person giving the report didn't think to say what color it was?
David S. Kong: What's that?
Mike Sackton: The person giving you the report didn't think to say what color it was?
David S. Kong: Dude, are you, like, the color eye police now? Like, what's the… what's your deal? Like, who's this guy? Like, Sculpit, what's the…
David S. Kong: Is that everybody has to like report, give the report exactly the way Sculpit wants to report? Is this what's going on?
Mike Sackton: It's okay. Let's go.
David S. Kong: The shaman, everybody, excitedly, Heads out of the tent, and you all make your way and fly.
David S. Kong: back to the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: And as you fly back to the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: What's so annoying about ImmersiveView is I have to resize these things every time.
Tim Sackton: See, this is why I don't bother.
David S. Kong: But the effect is so cool, to have the…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But.
David S. Kong: thing.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's that's pretty nuts what we're looking at here. I like it.
David S. Kong: and.
Eric Rosenbaum: Very AI.
David S. Kong: As you all, as you all, well, we all know AI is the killer app for D&D. D&D is the killer app for AI.
David S. Kong: You all fly back to, to the, to the Wanderer's Eye and another…
David S. Kong: It's a smaller group. There's like three or four dragonets up here, but the shaman flies, Uru flies with you, Roska.
David S. Kong: Everybody, there's probably about five other Dragonets in addition to the four of you here.
David S. Kong: And, you land, You know, in this spot, right next to the Wanderer's Eye.
David S. Kong: And it is open, and it looks basically kind of like what you're looking at. It's got these structures, just, like, very well-defined, like, mechanical structures that
David S. Kong: You know, there's like little parts of the island where you might see evidence of some things that look a little bit like this, but seeing it all kind of built into the iris of the eye.
David S. Kong: And you, first you see it from a distance, so you're flying in, you know, about like, you know, you're first like 500 feet away, 400, 300, you're kind of getting closer and closer.
David S. Kong: And… As you get closer, You notice that the wanderer's eye, the iris, is kind of dialing and it's
David S. Kong: Definitely feels like it's tracking you as you are getting closer.
Eric Rosenbaum: No.
Tim Sackton: Yes.
David S. Kong: What do you do?
Tim Sackton: I mean, as we're flying, I want to just ask the shaman, like, I mean, you know, genuine respect, like, what do you want us to do here? Like…
David S. Kong: Nobody knows what is going on.
David S. Kong: We… Are all in this, figuring this out right now.
David S. Kong: Whatever is happening, it seems like the island has some kind of a…
David S. Kong: Reaction to whatever the 4 of you are going and doing, something seems to be going on, I don't know what, but
David S. Kong: It feels like… You have a role to play in whatever's unfolding.
David S. Kong: I'll say it like that.
Eric Rosenbaum: Anybody want to talk to the statue?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Nice.
David S. Kong: Little Tony.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hmm.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Man, how do you even, how do you even talk to a statue? Hey.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hey, buddy! How… How's things? What…
Eric Rosenbaum: Ugh.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What's new? I see your eyes open. I'm Lil Tony. These are my guys. What's going on?
David S. Kong: So, so this is the wonder. I mean, this is this is your statue. Like, you're here all the time.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: What I love about it is that it is quiet. That is what the thing that you love most about this place is that it is quiet.
David S. Kong: And what you know… do you… so do you… do you… actually, make a… make an insight check.
David S. Kong: As you, as you try to address it.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Go, that's, 16?
David S. Kong: That's with your modifiers and everything? All in?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: The Wanderer, this place and this eye, I mean, all of these different parts of the Wanderer have always been just quiet. That's what you love about it.
David S. Kong: And what you sense as you get closer now and as you actually try to speak with it.
David S. Kong: Again, there are no words that Come.
David S. Kong: That come to you per se?
David S. Kong: But there is a feeling of great peace, like you feel like a sensation of peace.
David S. Kong: And you also hear a word.
David S. Kong: Like, resonating inside your mind.
David S. Kong: And it says… com.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, where?
David S. Kong: com.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Alright, the statue is telling us to go somewhere, come somewhere, .
David S. Kong: Where are you all now in relation to the eye?
Mike Sackton: I'm kind of pretty close to it, looking…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): her.
Mike Sackton: at it, right?
Tim Sackton: Yeah. I have like the group.
Mike Sackton: Steering up close at it, like, trying to inspect its mechanism and, like…
David S. Kong: So first, as you approach the eye, and I'm assuming, Tony, you started this conversation like as you were kind of approaching and getting closer.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: There were a couple of other dragonets, like, up at the eye, like, just trying to, like, kind of tapping at it, like, you know, like, kind of, like, just trying to do stuff with it, and nothing seems to be happening, but the eyes, like, kind of, again, it's just…
David S. Kong: The structures in it are kind of like worrying and moving and it's definitely like it feels like it's kind of tracking and like moving towards you or it's like looking at you somehow.
David S. Kong: As you're… as you're getting closer to it.
David S. Kong: And.
David S. Kong: As you land.
David S. Kong: Again, The… Tony, the voice in your head?
David S. Kong: It's definitely, like, you have, it's, it's, it's kind of eerie, because, again, you're so used to it being quiet, but the word, the word come, it's like this deep, low, super, super bassy, low, like, resonant, resonant sound that you haven't heard before, like, it's very, very low frequency come.
David S. Kong: And the eye is still kind of, like, like.
David S. Kong: It looks… it looks like it's definitely aware of your presence as you… as you approach.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So, here, you know, here…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Here we are and whatnot,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hope your day's been nice so far,
Tim Sackton: Does it, like, want some food or something?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, did you get any breakfast?
David S. Kong: As you get, who's the closest right now to the eye?
Tim Sackton: Not Heska.
David S. Kong: Not Heska, okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, probably little Tony, but I sort of, I'm sort of imagining like in the image here, we're all kind of close together.
David S. Kong: So Vilton is the closest?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: Well, Tony, as you get closer, like, within, like, 20 feet, like, the iris of the eye, because the iris of the eye basically kind of has this, like, large mechanical closure, but as you get closer to it, it just kind of…
David S. Kong: And now there's like the tiniest little hole there.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yo, let's go!
Eric Rosenbaum: goldust.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Go!
David S. Kong: Did you get closer?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes! There's, like, a door.
Eric Rosenbaum: the.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I have a giant statue, like, let's…
David S. Kong: what is going.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I'm flying in.
David S. Kong: Okay, all right.
Eric Rosenbaum: Zoom is. Zoom is.
David S. Kong: But just, just… so, Tony, do you, like, rush to the, to the opening of Vi?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, this is the coolest thing that has happened today.
David S. Kong: Okay, well, as, Tony, as you get closer, definitely the iris starts to open up. Like, it just, it just, it feels like, just as you're going, like, are you flying straight in towards the iris?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
David S. Kong: As you fly straight towards the iris, it starts to just, like, actually open and get larger and larger. And I think, as you, like, are you just gonna, like, like, what velocity are you flying towards the eye?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm gonna slow down enough to make sure that I'm not the only person flying through the eyeball.
David S. Kong: The giant statue.
Tim Sackton: I'm right behind you.
Mike Sackton: Can I, like, just teleport into it?
David S. Kong: Good question. Can you just, like, you can teleport into just a direction you don't know?
Mike Sackton: Like towards the eye, like with my newfound teleport skill, can I just like jump into the eye, just through the iris?
David S. Kong: You want to teleport through the iris?
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: You can try to do that. How would we… how would we do this, Mike? What's the best way for you to try to teleport into the Irish? Because one was the rolling the D4 to, like, do directionality, but then how do we, is there… is there a mechanic for quality of teleport?
David S. Kong: Because otherwise, I would say, like, maybe an insight check? Just as a part, just to see how well you teleport?
Mike Sackton: Sure. All right.
Mike Sackton: Yep.
David S. Kong: What are your role?
Mike Sackton: 22.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: Sculpa disappears. You little tongue.
Mike Sackton: I am going in when I before I do this.
David S. Kong: Okay, you say I'm going in?
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Lil Tony, you fly full speed and then Heska's behind you?
Tim Sackton: Yep.
David S. Kong: Where is, Zeno, where are you?
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm also going in as fast as possible. I'm just following the.
David S. Kong: three.
Eric Rosenbaum: Little 22.
David S. Kong: Fast as possible?
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay, you notice Roska also. So, just, just for a little context, Roska is, like, one of the best fighters on the island, as well. Like, he's, like, a ripped, like, buff, like, fighter, fighter guy.
David S. Kong: He's also, like, part of this group, and has also been, like, flying with you guys, along with the shaman.
David S. Kong: So…
David S. Kong: The 3 that are flying into the iris of the eye, make an acrobatics check, each of you.
Mike Sackton: I'll be right back, guys, sorry.
Mike Sackton: Especially if they're dealing with stuff.
Tim Sackton: 24.
David S. Kong: Nice.
David S. Kong: Tony?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): 10…
Eric Rosenbaum: 23.
David S. Kong: Do you have any way to juice up your tent?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I mean, I try real hard.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, oh, oh! I can,
Eric Rosenbaum: I have my thing that I can do.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Curse.
Tim Sackton: Wow.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, no, that's for myself. Hype Man.
Tim Sackton: that.
Eric Rosenbaum: Tony.
David S. Kong: Drop some hype, man.
Eric Rosenbaum: Flying into the eye.
Eric Rosenbaum: There is no do, only try. Oh shit, it's the other way around. Who knows what we will have found?
David S. Kong: inside.
Eric Rosenbaum: We're going for a ride.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): through that.
David S. Kong: Eye of the iris of the wanderer's eye. All right, Tony.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): He definitely feels better about himself after this.
David S. Kong: Damn.
Eric Rosenbaum: So that's a…
Tim Sackton: Out of D4.
Eric Rosenbaum: Added it for you.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's a 3 for 13.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice, nice.
David S. Kong: So basically,
David S. Kong: Heska, like, who was, like, second, just shoots by Tony, like, just, like, straight, beautiful, like, if only this had happened in the Jubilee Festival, like, moment, just darts, like a dart, right through into the center of the iris of the giant's eye, and just flies right through.
David S. Kong: Zeno, you also fly gracefully through the eye. Rosca, you hear him, like, behind, like, I'm coming too! And he also shoots through. The shaman is like, I'm not, but report back!
David S. Kong: And, you know, hangs back, and then little Tony, you shoot through.
David S. Kong: You're like, like, as you are flying through and shooting through, you kind of like, you know, like, knock against the side of the iris, like, as you're getting through and you get through it. But you also notice, like, basically as you go through, because you're the last one that ultimately made it in Rosca shot in right before you.
David S. Kong: The iris… Shuts closed.
David S. Kong: Behind all 5 of you.
David S. Kong: And as you, make it through…
David S. Kong: To the other side of the iris.
David S. Kong: You realize for a second, especially Sculpit and
David S. Kong: Tony, cause you're here at the Wanderer quite often, like
David S. Kong: Holy fuck. Just flew through the Wanderer's eyeball.
David S. Kong: Like, how are you even inside the Wanderer? Like, is this a thing? Like, is this like
David S. Kong: basically the coolest day that's ever happened. Like, you woke up in the morning, you imagined a fish inside of a fish with a potato, and that happened, and you ate that, and now you're flying into the iris of the water's eye? Like, this is a pretty fucking sick day.
David S. Kong: And as you fly through, Just a second here…
David S. Kong: you
David S. Kong: At first, you realize that you're in some kind of a shaft. It's actually, like, a long tunnel, and it's kind of spiraling and kind of twisting down, like a large… basically some kind of mechanical shaft that you're inside of.
David S. Kong: And as you're flying through, you notice something else, which is that as you go.
David S. Kong: It feels like the tunnel itself is activating.
David S. Kong: Like, as you're flying.
David S. Kong: Lights start turning on and that same humming frequency, Zeno, that you heard with the food machine.
David S. Kong: That, but, like…
David S. Kong: It's far more intense in amplitude, different frequencies, like, it's a cacophony of, like, sound and action as you're flying through the mechanical shaft.
David S. Kong: And…
Eric Rosenbaum: Hmm.
David S. Kong: As it gets louder and louder and more resonant as you go, and as lights turn on brighter and brighter as you fly.
David S. Kong: Through this whole system.
David S. Kong: You start to realize as you're flying through that whatever the hell is inside the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: I mean, most Dragonets, like.
David S. Kong: Everybody kind of thought these were just stone statues. You know, that was kind of the going thought.
Eric Rosenbaum: and.
David S. Kong: was that these things were all made of stone. And people would tell stories about these statues and, you know, kind of little vignettes of like what they maybe did one day and so on.
David S. Kong: But what you see inside is…
David S. Kong: Mind-boggling because you can't explain what these objects are and what the shapes are, you just have not seen materials that look like this with the smoothness and the colors and
David S. Kong: it's just everything is, like, so foreign and strange. It's like that food that you saw earlier, which is just like, who the who eats this food? Like, who would eat that?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And as you're flying through this, you're sensing to yourself, like.
David S. Kong: Whatever this is… It doesn't feel like it has to do with dragonets or anything.
Eric Rosenbaum: leaning.
David S. Kong: Culture, or anything you've seen, but…
David S. Kong: It is very weird and awesome.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And the other thing that happens as you fly.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You noticed for yourselves that sensation that you felt when you were
Audio shared by David S. Kong: After hugging the egg, and each of you had your own experience of sacredness, and you felt a sacred power entering your system.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You feel that again.
David S. Kong: And as you're flying through this tunnel.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And as the lights turn on and the machines start to whir, and as you also start to feel yourselves gain energy, strength, Heska, you're sharper, your vision, you're stronger, you're faster.
David S. Kong: Zeno, the music in your head, you feel like you could sing to these machines. You feel like you know the frequency of these machines. And if you knew exactly just before, like what kind of symphony that you wanted to sing to the mountain or to your fellow dragonettes, you feel like you could sing to these machines.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: Tony, same thing for you, suddenly it feels like
David S. Kong: Not that the machines are talking to you, but you have, if they were gonna say anything, you would definitely be able to understand it.
David S. Kong: And Sculpit, your sense, again, of this
David S. Kong: Traveling and movement and this kind of tumultuous magic energy that you have inside of you again feels like it's stabilized.
David S. Kong: And, all of you are now level 10.
Mike Sackton: Okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Awesome.
David S. Kong: For now, just,
Eric Rosenbaum: The.
David S. Kong: That's the main thing? Yeah, you're all level 10.
David S. Kong: So, main thing is hit points, but.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Feel free.
David S. Kong: You want to just, you know, like pick a cool thing that you want to either a cool spell. And this is also kind of like, you know, your characters don't like, it's like, so just you can pick like one cool thing, like out of anything you want that is a level 10 thing that your character class can do. And yeah.
David S. Kong: And also, it's good, because you don't have a lot of time to think about it anyways, so you're… but you're all level.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh my gosh.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm not prepared for this.
David S. Kong: anyways, don't worry too much about this right now. : The big thing is just character sheets make yourselves level 10, so you have level 10 hit points.
Eric Rosenbaum: So wait, how do I do that, even?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You click the little anvil.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: On the top right, and then you change your level to 10.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Boom. Done.
Eric Rosenbaum: 73 hit points.
Eric Rosenbaum: Word.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, magical secrets. Any two spells at all?
Mike Sackton: Yeah, Bart's level, that guy's got all kinds of good things.
David S. Kong: This is how we're going to do this. Literally spend three minutes, like right now, just like deciding if you're going to add a spell, like whatever. There's just you get whatever you get. But we're going to we're going to figure this out. Like you decide one thing and literally. Yeah, we'll spend 2 to 3 minutes figuring out something cool that you want to add for yourself as a level ten character.
David S. Kong: Does everybody feel like they've, like, picked something cool, or should we…
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I got it.
David S. Kong: Anyway, well, actually, you don't have to tell me, which is whatever it is, you can keep it to yourself.
Eric Rosenbaum: There's too many spells, I have no idea.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, it's unfair to Eric here.
David S. Kong: I.
Tim Sackton: Just whatever Seeker could do, you can now do.
Mike Sackton: Pick, pick, right, pick one of your favorite spells from Seeker.
Eric Rosenbaum: But just has to be very Zeno.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yes. What does that even mean?
Mike Sackton: Does it have to be that? I mean…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, no, wait, you don't have sixth level spells.
Tim Sackton: The Psychic Lance one is kind of Xeno. Like, play it as like a…
David S. Kong: Like, vicious mockery.
Tim Sackton: It's like super amped, vicious mockery.
David S. Kong: Sick burn. It's sick burn, like, ultra amps. That's good.
Eric Rosenbaum: Alright, I'll just take just that one, maybe.
David S. Kong: That's perfect.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, that's fine.
David S. Kong: Tony, do you have a, do you have something?
Tim Sackton: This is not… it's not really.
Mike Sackton: Firefox.
Tim Sackton: Because…
Mike Sackton: Fireball's not a bad choice.
Mike Sackton: Take Fireball with your, with your thingies.
Mike Sackton: Your magical secrets.
Tim Sackton: See, I…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Tim Sackton: Just dead.
Tim Sackton: I just took all of my traits.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you Yeah.
Tim Sackton: Okay, I'm done.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'm stopping.
David S. Kong: DM cheating. Not even.
Tim Sackton: the.
David S. Kong: Extra, extra, extra insight. All right.
Tim Sackton: Rogues are actually pretty easy, though.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: So let's, let's move on. Let's move on. Schwartz, you got something you can roll on?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, I'll get there.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, alright, keep thinking about it, you have a little bit of time.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, as you, continue to fly through this structure.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You end up in a new space that's
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You can see, approaching from above, I'm gonna change this view a bit, just so you can kind of approximately see what this is, but…
David S. Kong: But you're approaching this scene from above, so just kind of ignore the background a little bit.
David S. Kong: You're flying above this.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And you see these 4 enormous statues seated in a quadrant.
David S. Kong: and this huge antechamber and a room above, and… and you're… you're seeing this from above right now, so you're flying… you can… and now Heska, with 10th level perception, you know, you can see this first before everybody else, the…
David S. Kong: The size and scope of these structures that are down below you.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, my passive perception is 19 now.
David S. Kong: Yes, exactly, so you can, you see this, you see this, from a ways away.
David S. Kong: What, what are you, do you guys still like flying full force towards all this or what's your, what are you, what are you doing?
Tim Sackton: Yeah, husk is feeling awesome. He's like what?
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Tim Sackton: Is.
David S. Kong: Is everybody, is everybody, is everybody flying full force?
Eric Rosenbaum: We were on to something with the fish inside of fish. It's statues inside of statues.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes. And inside that statue, a potato.
Eric Rosenbaum: Probably.
David S. Kong: Tony, Tony, make that.
Tim Sackton: Is there a potato?
David S. Kong: Tony, make an insight check.
Eric Rosenbaum: We should check.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Here we go.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That is, 17.
David S. Kong: You hear, a very clear
David S. Kong: voice, but it's also, like, voices in your head. Like, you all haven't gotten, you know, all the way to… but this is as you're kind of realizing the scene. Heska sees it first, and then, as you're… as you're probably, like, 100 feet, or… say, how far… how far… how far can Dragonites fly? It's, like, 30… 30 feet per second?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, but.
Tim Sackton: It's pretty fast, like, it's decently fast.
David S. Kong: You, in your mind, Tony, hear several words all kind of together.
David S. Kong: One is…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Defend?
David S. Kong: Another.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: is, safe.
David S. Kong: And another is intruder.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): No, no, no, no, we're friends, we're friends, we're friends, we're friends. Hey, we haven't introduced ourselves. It's very good to meet you. My name's Little Tony. These are my companions. This is a pleasure to meet you.
David S. Kong: Are you all still flying full speed?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): also.
David S. Kong: Sorry, sorry, sorry. Actually, one other thing, one other thing. The other thing that happens when you all became level 10 as you were flying through the mechanical shop.
David S. Kong: Tony.
David S. Kong: So, your ability to, again, commune with objects and so on. You find now that you actually are able to commune with your friends.
David S. Kong: And that you are actually able to hear into their minds and
David S. Kong: It's just an intuition, but you feel like if you said something to your friends in your mind.
David S. Kong: They would be able to talk back to you and if they kind of were thinking about you as they were talking that they could kind of talk to you and maybe everybody else.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes. Guys, we should have a chat. We should, we'll slow down. We should, like, let's, let's, let's have a little conversation with, with our new friends and, you know.
David S. Kong: How many feet away from me are you slowing down? Are you slowing down? Is everybody slowing down? What's happening?
Mike Sackton: If… sure.
Tim Sackton: Slow down.
David S. Kong: But how far are you, how far away from you and how far away are when you slow down, Heska?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Dude, like a… 100 feet.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: All right, let's roll initiative.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, boy.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's a five.
Tim Sackton: That's a 20.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hold on, Tim…
David S. Kong: Hold on, Heska is what? Heska is 20?
Tim Sackton: Yep.
Mike Sackton: I got a 15.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Shh.
David S. Kong: 15, that is, Sculpit.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's a 23 for me.
David S. Kong: 23 for Tony.
David S. Kong: And then,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What is that for you?
David S. Kong: Zeno?
Eric Rosenbaum: Big Five.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What is it?
Eric Rosenbaum: 5.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: And… alright, cool.
David S. Kong: Give me one second here, I gotta roll…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Bunch of initiatives, also for.
David S. Kong: Roscoe, by the way, is also,
David S. Kong: He's very good at acrobatics and is keeping, keeping up. Hold on, let me just roll…
David S. Kong: But I could believe.
David S. Kong: for… Oh, can I just do… I can do it 3 times, great.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That's nice.
David S. Kong: 18… And just give me one more second.
David S. Kong: Hmm.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: Alright, everybody. So, as soon as you get to 100 feet.
David S. Kong: Just give me one more second here…
David S. Kong: As soon as you get within 100 ft, all 4 of the statues look up at you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They don't move, but they definitely look up.
David S. Kong: And, their eyes light up.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: and… Get here…
David S. Kong: I'm very proud of myself for this.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And we have a dollar now.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: All right.
David S. Kong: So,
David S. Kong: The statues… the statues look up at, each of the four of you, and just, I think we'll just… just… if you… we'll kind of do honor system here, just so you can put your cursor on, like, where… where your… where your spot is. This is not in D&D Beyond, obviously, this is in this, so just… just, you know, kind of keep track of your location as you're flying down.
David S. Kong: But, as soon as you guys get to within 100 feet.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Let me just check the initiative order…
David S. Kong: Heska, you go first.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What do you do?
Tim Sackton: Okay, so these statues are moving? What are the statues?
David S. Kong: They're not moving. They're not moving. They're not moving at all. All their their their eyes activated red, and they're looking at you. They're looking at at well, they're looking up.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, it's hard to know exactly what they're looking at, but they're looking up.
Tim Sackton: And how big are they?
David S. Kong: They're… they're huge. They're not… I mean, these are, like, probably, yeah, like, 100 feet tall?
Tim Sackton: Shouldn't we run, guys?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Eric Rosenbaum: What,
Tim Sackton: I'm gonna look for somewhere to hide, anything I can duck behind that would provide cover.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: Not where you are. You'd have to like kind of go to the side of the mechanical. Like you'd have to like, right now you're kind of in the middle of the shaft flying down. So you could kind of like on the edges, but right now you're like literally barreling down through the middle of the…
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I'm happy to go to an edge if I can reach it.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: So you move towards an edge?
Tim Sackton: I move towards an edge if there's somewhere I can hide, and I'm gonna hide.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Tim Sackton: Sackton hide.
Tim Sackton: That's a 25.
David S. Kong: Add us for what?
Tim Sackton: Hi.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, to hide, okay, okay. Alright, excellent.
David S. Kong: that's good.
David S. Kong: Oh, actually, I'm so sorry, Tony. You should have gone first. My bad, my bad. But let's do Heska, then Tony. That's fine. You can hide. Tony, you're actually up first, but you go next.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And… I think as my action, I'll… Drop of…
Tim Sackton: Fog cloud on top of the head of one of the statues.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, excellent.
Tim Sackton: Which is…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's a 20 foot radius, so just like a big cloud of
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Do I recognize any of the statues? Like, what are.
Tim Sackton: Are these like miniatures of the?
David S. Kong: These are not, these are not.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: They're not, well, they're not miniatures of any of the divine statues that you can recognize, but there are like kind of like vibes of the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: Like, these definitely look more like battle statues. Like, they look more like they're ready to fight. But they have, like, some aesthetic that connects to the Wanderer. It's not, like, exactly the Wanderer, but it's like if the Wanderer had a bunch of guards that were wearing, that were part of his same squad.
David S. Kong: Kind of thing. Okay.
Tim Sackton: Well…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: gonna…
Tim Sackton: pick one of them at random, because I don't know anything that distinguishes it, and put… make… summon a cloud of fog that will…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Envelop its head.
Tim Sackton: And some distance around it.
David S. Kong: So let's just pick one from this view, Tim. Which one do you want?
Tim Sackton: Okay, this one, this one here, the upper left.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Upper left. Okay, upper left one has fog.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Excellent.
David S. Kong: Little Tony, you're up.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Okay, what I want to do is try to chat with these guys.
David S. Kong: Nice, okay, okay.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Get them to,
David S. Kong: excellent.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): helpful to me. What I would really like, and I don't know mechanically if this is possible, is for my familiar to assist me in this.
David S. Kong: Yeah, sure.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): My.
David S. Kong: Is your… where's your familiar?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So, my familiar is Glenda the Seagull.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And,
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's complicated because,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Glenda…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I don't really care for her, but she's infatuated with me, and I… I feel awkward about this because she's magically bound to me, and, like, the inherent power differential…
David S. Kong: Very odd situation we've got here.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, I got it, yeah. So there's an increasingly…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): elaborate web of deception about how I am in another relationship, because I also sort of want to let her down gently, and she's, like, really useful as a familiar.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But, because I have the familiar friend feet.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As a…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Something. I get advantage when she is within 5 feet of me, and I'm using a skill in which I have a proficiency. Love it. I can use it…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): The number of times equal to my proficiency bonus. So, what I really want to do here is, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: have Glenda…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Flying next to me and it's like circling up with me and and I'm trying to.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, not be in combat and instead, like, open, open, like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Communication, like, let's not have a fight about this. Like, we're all just guys.
David S. Kong: Yeah, make a wisdom, another insight check with advantage.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Because you're gonna try to… you're basically gonna try to communicate with the statues.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I…
David S. Kong: You spend your action trying to do that.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's exactly right. Do you want me to make insight or persuasion?
David S. Kong: Up to you, your choice.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: actually it's entirely identical so I'm gonna do that, I'm gonna do it with advantage because I'm using, because Glenn does, Glenn is like giving me a little bit of coaching on.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): On how to have the conversation with them.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, great.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The first roll is a…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 11, which is not ideal, and the second roll is, 14.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Oh.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Also not…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Great!
David S. Kong: Yeah, I mean, you basically get the same message of,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Defend. Safe.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Intruder.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But it's weird, like, just thinking you, little Tony, like yourself.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Weirdly, like the intruder kind of energy, it's like.
David S. Kong: Weirdly, like, not directed at you, like, you're kind of like, it's sort of like, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Intruder, but…
David S. Kong: You don't necessarily feel like you're an intruder, like you're kind of like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, this is… I mean, it's, it's hard to totally say, but you're just kind of You know
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That's kind of the energy you get.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: on this Alright.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'll just shout out like it's not obvious they're trying to fight us.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, Sonata Pistona.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Just leave it there, that's right.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Alright, the next… The act is statue number one.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, so upper right Tim has a fog on it. What's the effect of the fog?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Heavily obscured, so it can't see anything outside of the cloud.
Tim Sackton: But it doesn't follow it, so if it can move, it can move outside of the fog cloud.
David S. Kong: What does it do to the vision?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Just.
Tim Sackton: Blinded, it can't see anything.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, okay, cool.
David S. Kong: Okay, yeah, the one that is, the statue that's in the fog cloud,
David S. Kong: Nothing happens. Doesn't do anything.
David S. Kong: The next statue…
David S. Kong: Which is the lower… upper left statue. You see, again, all of its… all eight of them, or all four of them, their eyes lit up. This one, eyes light up red, and it shoots a…
David S. Kong: Beam of energy from its eyeballs.
David S. Kong: up towards… Rosca.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
Mike Sackton: Is Roscoe the bad guy?
David S. Kong: Mrs.
David S. Kong: But it gets two attacks.
David S. Kong: It rolls again.
David S. Kong: Oh, that also… Rosca, like, dodges, like, like, both, like, they're big energy beams, but, like, manages to dodge, both of them.
David S. Kong: The second one, Nixon, just a little bit.
David S. Kong: And then it's now the third statue.
David S. Kong: And this statue… Also misses… First attack, and second attack.
David S. Kong: Oh This one, it has a huge blast of energy and hits Raska square in the chest.
David S. Kong: Doing… I don't understand what this is doing… Oh, man, 28 damage.
David S. Kong: Rosca is badly wounded from this,
David S. Kong: Up next is sculpting.
Mike Sackton: The sculpit will.
Mike Sackton: Cast…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hello?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I don't really wanna…
Mike Sackton: Fight these things, necessarily. I'll cast Mirror Image.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, 3… Duplicates of Sculpit appear floating around next to him.
Mike Sackton: And.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And then…
Mike Sackton: And then, wait, who hasn't gone yet?
Eric Rosenbaum: I have also.
David S. Kong: One more Sacho and Zeno and Roscoe.
Mike Sackton: I'll, I'll give a Bardic Inspiration die to… to…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zita? Zita?
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, word. Thank you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 1v10 now?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And take, do a good job!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you Something good!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Ed.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Well, that's it.
Mike Sackton: And then I'll,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Kind of.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I can't really hide. I'll… Yeah, that's it.
David S. Kong: And then, let's see, it is now,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Zeno's turn.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So Zeno's down at the bottom left, approaching one of the statues.
Eric Rosenbaum: And he's feeling big and bold.
Eric Rosenbaum: Gets right up in his face, not too close.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But he's like.
Eric Rosenbaum: I say swing, you say stick! Swing!
David S. Kong: Stick.
Eric Rosenbaum: So he's doing the call and his call and response. Nice.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Talent.
David S. Kong: And the statue does have a stick. The statue does have a stick, so.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, if I use my action for a call… oh, it's.
Eric Rosenbaum: Wisdom saving throw against spell ability. What is spell ability?
Tim Sackton: That's just your normal, your normal save, whatever it is for your spells. Just say it's like…
Tim Sackton: Say it's, like…
Eric Rosenbaum: It says save DC 15.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, but it should be higher than that at level 10, so it's like…
Mike Sackton: Wow, that's only if you… that's only if we get level up, only if we do stats.
Mike Sackton: Did you go and take feats and bump your stats and all that stuff?
Tim Sackton: Well, because I did it very quickly, but Eric did it very slowly, so I don't know if it's fair.
Mike Sackton: Scott, I interpreted the pick one thing as pick one thing, not as many things as I can do in two minutes.
Tim Sackton: Well, rogues, to be fair, rogues don't get much except for…
David S. Kong: Okay, okay, okay.
Tim Sackton: RTS.
David S. Kong: Let's move on here. Eric, so…
Tim Sackton: Make it like a 16.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: and.
David S. Kong: Oh, is that for me? For me at 16, you're saying?
Eric Rosenbaum: See?
Tim Sackton: Roll a statue.
Eric Rosenbaum: you.
Tim Sackton: Roll a wisdom saving throw.
Eric Rosenbaum: against 16.
David S. Kong: Oh, 19, sorry.
Eric Rosenbaum: Swing, you say!
Mike Sackton: I will, I will, I will cast Silvery Barbs.
David S. Kong: What does that mean?
Eric Rosenbaum: too.
Tim Sackton: the.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Amen.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh, nice, nice.
David S. Kong: Got you.
Tim Sackton: Don't forget, you can use… Sick burn.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh… minus 1D.
Mike Sackton: Oh, and actually…
Eric Rosenbaum: as a reaction.
Mike Sackton: Wait, wait, wait, wait, I shouldn't do Silvery Barbs.
Tim Sackton: No, you should do.
Mike Sackton: I should do cutting work.
Tim Sackton: Do what Finnan did. You should do cutting words. Actually.
Mike Sackton: you do cutting.
Tim Sackton: Also has cutting words. You can both cutting words.
Mike Sackton: Wait, we're both war bards?
David S. Kong: Ha ha ha ha!
Mike Sackton: You college afford to, Eric.
Eric Rosenbaum: I don't even know.
David S. Kong: Okay, so what's happening? You guys are both…
Mike Sackton: No, no, no, I'm doing cutting words instead of summary barbs.
David S. Kong: Okay.
Mike Sackton: the.
Tim Sackton: Oh no, Eric, Eric, you're not College of.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, I roll…
Mike Sackton: Actually, no, I'm gonna stick with Silvery Barbs. Okay. Just roll, roll, roll again, roll again.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I roll again.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 4. Wasatchi fails.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What happens now?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Well, when I say swing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You say stick. Stick. Swing.
David S. Kong: Stick!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Sway.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Exactly.
Mike Sackton: And…
David S. Kong: How much damage?
Tim Sackton: It doesn't do damage. It just has to, it's in a, it's in a call and response with Zeno. It has to use its action.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It can't do anything but that.
Tim Sackton: I can't do anything else.
David S. Kong: The ancient mechanical statue is now trapped in a freestyle battle with Zeno. Okay.
Mike Sackton: Aska also, the glow of this, you have advantage.
David S. Kong: to Jenna next.
David S. Kong: Dragonet Battle, alright.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Rosca now is gonna act.
David S. Kong: Roska is just a classic fighter, so he is not deterred by this whole situation at all and dives towards the statue that is in the rap battle and tries to attack it.
David S. Kong: He's got a short start with him.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: He misses.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And that's the end of his turn. Okay, the last statue, now also Alright.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Turns on its laser beam eyes, and also attacks shooting beams at Roska.
Mike Sackton: I think Roscoe's the problem here, guys.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I agree too.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: One, he misses, the second one…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Second one hits.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: This one does… 10 more damage… Roska is bloody, guys. He is definitely, in rough-looking shape.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Hong, is the iris still open?
David S. Kong: It closed behind you.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, it closed when we came in.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Can any of us get him out of here?
Mike Sackton: Only if I go with him.
Mike Sackton: Oh, but… and he'd have to be willing.
Mike Sackton: Wait, what's Dimension Door?
Mike Sackton: It's willing, right? Dimension door is willing.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What's the iris made out of? What material?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Is it stone, by any chance?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Right.
Mike Sackton: Oh, but I have tons of spell slots. I can Dimension Thor twice.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Going from third to… 10th level, all of a sudden you're just showering with spell slots.
David S. Kong: ready?
David S. Kong: So it's Tony, it's back, back to you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay,
Mike Sackton: You want to convince Rosca that he needs to get out of here. I can take him.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, I'll do that. I'll, I'm gonna persuade Rosca. Say, Rosca! Rosca!
Mike Sackton: Okay, also…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Be persuasive.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): First of all, I am so impressed by everything that you're contributing. I think you're doing a really terrific job.
Eric Rosenbaum: Second point is…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): say you have to leave immediately or you're gonna die. But third, in conclusion, I just really want to emphasize how impressed I am with everything that you're bringing to the team right now.
David S. Kong: Roll a persuasion check.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That is 18 altogether.
David S. Kong: Do you do this in a freestyle? Because that's how he responds the best.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Wait, wait, how do I do this?
David S. Kong: Are you doing this to him and Ryan? Because that's how he responds, Roscoe responds the best.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yes, I mean, of course I am.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: My name is Lil Tony, and I'm here to say, Rosca, you gotta get outta here in a major way.
David S. Kong: you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Because you're inside getting chopped to bits.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We gotta get you out to save your tits!
David S. Kong: Roska hearing these words and he's bloodied and is like, like kind of like, oh shit, why the fuck are all these statues shooting laser beams at me?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: is he looks up at, you, little Tony, and he's like, my name is Roska, and I'm here to say I'm getting the hell out of here. Help me, please, anyway.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And is, like, looking up, like, get me the hell out of here, guys.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Tony, are you doing anything else for your turn?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, I mean, I'll fly up, can I, like, fly up and…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Grab him and start… Heading out? I mean, the…
David S. Kong: Oh, it turns out you actually… you're gonna use Move and get down there and actually grab them?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, I think so, and sorry.
Mike Sackton: Are you taking it?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Back towards the iris.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: We're back up.
David S. Kong: Right now, you're in range, like…
Mike Sackton: Is the IRS open? I thought the IRS was closed.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: No, no. No, but my thinking is, like, it's…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We know it's an exit, maybe if I get close to it, it'll open again.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I mean, I can just teleport out and back in with Dimension Door, and it's okay.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, but it's more… it's more of right now, Roska is, like, in laser beam range of all four statues, and is, like, you know, went into melee against one of the statues. So Tony, trying to pull him out of the melee is…
Mike Sackton: Yeah, yeah, do that. Bring him back up to, like, same place person's face.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So 10 minutes ago, your greatest asset was the ability to provide cogent feedback to others. Like, I don't know that you can teleport.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Maybe.
Mike Sackton: No, I'm speaking! Can't we talk in each other's minds? I'm telling you that!
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. By the way, just yeah. After you turned level 10, Tony enabled telepathic communication. You can all communicate telepathically.
Mike Sackton: I thought, no, no, no, this was like what Sculpin is saying to you in your mind.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Gotcha, got.
David S. Kong: you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: All right.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): hell.
David S. Kong: So you use your move to pull Roscoe? Yeah. How many feet can you get him up?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Third… 30?
David S. Kong: Okay, all right. He is still in laser range, unfortunately, but Huska, it's your turn.
Tim Sackton: Oh.
David S. Kong: And so now, just to clarify, now both Tony and Rosca are in laser range. Everybody else is not.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Fair enough.
Tim Sackton: So the first thing I'm gonna do.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you .
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So I… so…
Tim Sackton: Maybe this is unfair. One of the feats I took was observant that lets me.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: make…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Search action is a bonus action. The first thing I want to do is just like look around, like.
Tim Sackton: Can I tell if these statues are.
Eric Rosenbaum: and.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, they… At least our impression is that they seem to be targeting.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Roscoe, specifically.
Tim Sackton: Like, is there anything I can see about them that would, or about the.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: While.
Tim Sackton: Still remaining…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: hidden.
Tim Sackton: About the environment that would suggest anything about a targeting mechanism, like.
David S. Kong: Hmm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Tim Sackton: Is it just, are they just like, are their heads just like looking up and shooting laser beams out of their eyes?
David S. Kong: Their bodies have not moved at all. Only their heads have been rotating. Like their heads are active and they're looking around. And yes, they have only, all four of them have only fired lasers at Rosca. There's been eight shots fired, all of them have been at Rosca.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
Tim Sackton: I have plenty of spell slots, even as a pathetic little third caster, so I am gonna waste a spell slot recasting Fog Cloud on Rosca.
Eric Rosenbaum: Oh.
David S. Kong: Nice. Okay.
Tim Sackton: But, remaining… Hit end.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: So now do the statues have disadvantage if they're shooting at them?
Tim Sackton: Yes.
David S. Kong: Excellent.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, that's…
Tim Sackton: Amazing job remembering the rules!
David S. Kong: I didn't know this intuition D&D. I'm just I'm vibe coding D&D right now, like DMing.
Tim Sackton: No, you're doing great. I'm just saying that was, that's exactly the correct rule.
David S. Kong: Perfect.
Tim Sackton: You know more than you think!
David S. Kong: Alright, is that the end of your turn?
Tim Sackton: Yeah, that's the end of my chart.
David S. Kong: Statue, the 1st statue, is gonna shoot again 2 times, but now, because you're, Tony, you and,
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And,
David S. Kong: Rosca are in a group together.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, but the fog cloud should cover both of them.
David S. Kong: Yeah, totally.
Tim Sackton: It's like 40 foot big.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: So, the first one… oh, 20, but…
Tim Sackton: disadvantage.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Advantage!
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh-ho-ho! He misses.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The second statue, rolls again… oh, disadvantage sucks! 13, and the second one…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, 18, you got the 13, that also misses. And then the last statue… 18 and…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Or the third statue.
David S. Kong: Oh, actually, this one was already in the fog. How long does the fog last?
Tim Sackton: No, no, I recast the spell, so it disappears from its concentration, so I can only have one fog cloud in it.
David S. Kong: So this one hits.
Tim Sackton: So all four of them can attack now.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah, this one, this one hits, but this one hits little Tony.
David S. Kong: Little Tony, this does…
Mike Sackton: Wait, I'm gonna… I'm gonna do my cutting works, then.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, what does that do?
Mike Sackton: I don't want little Tony to get hurt. I roll 1d10 and subtract it from…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Your role?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Tell me.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: 10. He misses! Well done! Okay!
Mike Sackton: I will shout out, not little Tony.
David S. Kong: Wait, it also works better in a rhyme, Mike. It also works better in a rhyme.
Tim Sackton: So.
David S. Kong: Cutting word, right.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh god.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Little… I don't know if I could ride, my brain is currently…
Mike Sackton: Shot with AI generated specs,
Mike Sackton: I'm trying to think of what I would miss. Hit, don't, don't…
Mike Sackton: Let little Toadie get hit. That would ruin the bit.
David S. Kong: Amazing. The 10 lands. The laser avoids, dodges, hits through the mist.
David S. Kong: It looked like a perfect strike, but just curved out of the way. And this is both Little Tony and Rosca.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And finally, we are at Sculpit. Sculpit, it is your turn.
David S. Kong: Mike, sculpt it.
Mike Sackton: I'm gonna dimension, I'm gonna go grab Little Tony and be like, not Little Tony,
David S. Kong: Roscoe.
Mike Sackton: I'd be like, you wanna get outta here?
David S. Kong: Dude, I fucking said that shit already in my rhyme. What are you doing? Let's go.
Mike Sackton: dimension door to go 500 feet straight up.
Mike Sackton: Which is presumably out of here.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, like 500 feet out of the statue? Yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay?
David S. Kong: Rosca and Sculpa disappear.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Then I'll cast it again.
Mike Sackton: I'll let Roska go. I'll say, Roska.
Mike Sackton: I don't think she'd come back in.
David S. Kong: Ross was like, I'm not trying to go back inside.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, exactly. Does the iris open if I fly up to it again?
David S. Kong: Yes, it does.
Mike Sackton: No, that'll just fly back in.
David S. Kong: So, as soon as, Rosca dimension doors out.
David S. Kong: All four of the statues, their eyes reset to blue.
David S. Kong: And…
Mike Sackton: Oh.
David S. Kong: Laser beams all stop.
Eric Rosenbaum: But I keep doing call and response, just because…
David S. Kong: Our brand. The statue still continues to call and response with you.
David S. Kong: And basically, you know, this… this is approximately the scene, as you all get to this stage, and it's… there's definitely, like, a big staircase, like, leading up into a large…
David S. Kong: A large chamber area, and you can tell
David S. Kong: Just kind of estimating, you're probably in the wanderer's chest right now.
David S. Kong: If you were to kind of map it.
David S. Kong: And, and again, now that, you have removed Rosca from this scene.
David S. Kong: Actually, what are you all, what are you all doing? You're, cause you're all, you're all hovering above right now, so what, what is, what is happening actually? You actually don't come all the way down here yet, so what are you doing?
Tim Sackton: Tusk is still hiding for the moment.
David S. Kong: Haskell's such a cat.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Dragonets are such cats, it's amazing.
Eric Rosenbaum: So good.
Eric Rosenbaum: This is weird, you guys.
Tim Sackton: But I assume we can all still talk telepathically, right?
David S. Kong: Yeah, you can also talk telepathically, but where are you all physically relative to the statues?
Tim Sackton: Their house is probably about 30 feet above them, and, like.
Tim Sackton: Like, inside one of these, like…
Tim Sackton: Window-like things on the side, hiding behind a pillar.
David S. Kong: One of the statues, Heska, is tracking you.
David S. Kong: Just kind of moving its head and looking, but that's it, just looking.
David S. Kong: What is everybody else doing?
Eric Rosenbaum: I'm circling my way down to the floor.
Eric Rosenbaum: But I'll probably.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): On the floor, this is where I just was, and like, waving up and introducing myself to each of the statues, whether or not.
Eric Rosenbaum: can.
David S. Kong: Bonnie, as you get closer,
David S. Kong: Now you, you hear in your heads, still.
David S. Kong: defend.
David S. Kong: Safe.
David S. Kong: But No more intruder.
David S. Kong: And, now, also, welcome.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Aww, that's so sweet of you guys. Thank you. You have a beautiful home. This is magnificent. I just, I love it. It's great to be here.
David S. Kong: There's, there's no, there's no, like, response from any of the statues, but,
David S. Kong: It's a little intense, Tony. All four of the statues, like, turn their heads and look at you. Like, they're all… eight eyes are… eight eyeballs are directly on little Tony, and then all in a synchronized way.
David S. Kong: They all… Nod their heads and about.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So I'll bow to each of them in turn. Like, yeah, you guys are like, you're like a low drama bunch. I respect that. I respect that. Like, if you're going to be roommates like this for however long you've been here, like, you gotta, you just gotta keep it really chill with each other.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I see it. I see you guys.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: The only, you hear just in a response again, this like feeling.
David S. Kong: Welcome.
David S. Kong: How's everybody else doing?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Well, where… where to?
Tim Sackton: So, you said one of the statues is tracking Seems like it's tracking me.
David S. Kong: Just, it was just, it was just watching as you landed, but then, you know, then, then it, it went and looked at, shipped it all to, to Little Tony and everybody bowed at Little Tony.
Tim Sackton: So so it's not like there's one statue that's paying particular attention to me. It's just okay.
David S. Kong: It's just while you were moving, it was…
Eric Rosenbaum: the.
David S. Kong: So you in particular, Heska, just caught it. Like, I think everybody else might have.
Tim Sackton: Right, right.
David S. Kong: that.
Tim Sackton: Right.
David S. Kong: But you have ultra perception now, so.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What do you all do?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, and by the way, the stairs and like all of the structures here.
David S. Kong: It's weird. Like they're not sized for you. It's like everything is just like a little bit bigger. It's like just, but not like, like crazy bigger. Like not, it's definitely not made for these statues either, but it's like just a size.
Eric Rosenbaum: select.
David S. Kong: Kind of like double size, like whatever, whatever is normally here, it's like just a little bit bigger than what you're used to.
David S. Kong: But they're clear steps, like leading up into what you guess would be the heart of the Wanderer.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Based on your location.
Eric Rosenbaum: I like looking at.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Statues. Like, can we go there?
David S. Kong: Are you saying the same thing?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Tim Sackton: No, to the statues pointing at the steps. Is is that okay?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hmm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You're saying that out loud? Yeah.
David S. Kong: You…
Tim Sackton: I'm not gonna do anything without asking permission.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, no, no, that's very wise, very wise. The statues, they don't say anything verbally.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But, so this is interesting. You, heska.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Receive.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: A kind of warm feeling.
David S. Kong: And also the word in your head.
Tim Sackton: I'll like start slowly walking up the stairs.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As you walk up the stairs.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Another thing, because the crazy thing was, you're literally, like, falling through this dark, like, mechanical shop, and as you're falling, is, like, lighting up and, like, getting crazy as you're falling through.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As you start walking up the steps, you notice as well, like, each step is like a…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: There's, like, a resonant sound, like.
David S. Kong: As each step is going, it's almost like, you know, in Big, like, the piano, like, you're, like, walking up this, like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Resonant piano, like, each step that you take.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, beautiful… like, it's almost as if there's, like, some kind of beautiful reverberation and echo each step you take up the stairs.
Tim Sackton: We're in a motion for Zoom.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Burp.
Tim Sackton: Xeno to come over.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: Xenora.
Tim Sackton: Listen to… listen to this!
Tim Sackton: And I like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
Tim Sackton: Do a little dance on the stairs.
Tim Sackton: China.
David S. Kong: As you did, it's like, it's like…
Tim Sackton: No musical talent whatsoever, but just like experimenting.
David S. Kong: Theirs are responsive and it's Xeno4View. It's not like music you've heard before per se, but it's like…
David S. Kong: Very lovely. It's like, it's bringing you back into like the heart space of like the egg, you know, that feeling of the egg.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: For sure.
Eric Rosenbaum: I wonder if they'd let us install like a kitchen here.
David S. Kong: you The restaurant concept never dies.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): We don't want our guests to be laser beamed though, like that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you.
David S. Kong: You hear another voice in your head, Tony?
Eric Rosenbaum: there.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Welcome.
Tim Sackton: We're gonna, like, motion everybody, like, I really wanna go see once.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, yeah, let's go, let's go.
Tim Sackton: Like if they're not stopped, I'm like going very cautiously because I want to make sure the statues aren't trying to stop us.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: you But Tesca's like… What is this? Like, there's something weird up here. Let's go see what it is.
David S. Kong: So to all four of you, go.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
David S. Kong: So as you step into the chamber, into what you assume is the heart of the Wanderer.
David S. Kong: And again, it's… it's… this whole area, it's kind of… the whole system is kind of crazy around in this area, with all of these structures.
David S. Kong: But as you step in, You see a room.
David S. Kong: That looks like this, approximately.
David S. Kong: And there's 8 seats.
David S. Kong: Around this circle.
David S. Kong: And what's strange to you, as you get closer and look at these seats, is that…
David S. Kong: They're sized perfectly for you.
David S. Kong: Like, the other structures in this whole place that you had seen felt like they were built for something that was bigger.
David S. Kong: But what's really weird is… yeah.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: These look perfectly sized for you.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And in fact, each of you feels…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, just almost like a little pull towards…
David S. Kong: a few of these chairs. Like, there's… one for each of them feels like it's… there's a little energy behind it that's saying.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Welcome.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I'll go to mine.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: Ask us how I'm gonna sit down.
Tim Sackton: Maybe we can control a statue from here.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What's that?
Eric Rosenbaum: Okay.
Tim Sackton: Maybe we can control the statue from here, heska's going to say.
Eric Rosenbaum: I wonder if it can walk. That'd be cool.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: everybody.
Eric Rosenbaum: Or maybe it shoots really big laser beams out of its eye.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Maybe it can catch fish!
Tim Sackton: And then shoot laser beams to cook.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Wait, wait, wait, hold on. So, so, one thing at a time. So, so…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You sit down into your chair and again, you notice as you sit down, like that feeling of like welcome.
David S. Kong: It's weird.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It's like, when you sit down, like, you know you've never been here before. Like, it's impossible that you've ever… it's like, you're inside, like, you flew through the fucking iris of the Wanderer, you, like, saw these giant, like, you know, like, statues shooting laser beams, and now you're sitting in the… it's like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And…
David S. Kong: Part of you is like, you know there's no possible way that.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Been here before?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Yet, when you sit down in the.
David S. Kong: share.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like…
David S. Kong: Chair you're sitting in.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Each welcomed you in.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It feels like… comfortable
Audio shared by David S. Kong: worn chair that you've been sitting in your whole life that is just your favorite chair. And it's like this timeless essence of chair that like when you're an old dragonet and on your dying days, you're going to want to sit in a fucking chair that is this chair.
David S. Kong: And there's something about that familiar.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And comfort as you sink into your chair.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Just feels… Like, home.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What do you do?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And.
David S. Kong: Jessica, you can go back to your conversation.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: of saying whatever you're saying. Yeah, I mean, I'm like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I guess at this point, I'm just waiting for something
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But are y'all doing anything or just sitting? What's your state of mind? What's everybody?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: feeling… Are you just… what's, yeah, what are you all doing?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As you said. You know, it's had, like, big day, weird breakfast.
Eric Rosenbaum: Better take an.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay, sleep.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Dina starts to take a little nap.
David S. Kong: Haska, what are you doing?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I mean, Heska is still like.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You know, imagining in his mind, like.
Tim Sackton: the giant hand like reaching down and scooping up this like giant hand of fish and then.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: holding it out and the laser beams shooting at the fish.
Tim Sackton: and making like fish barbecue and then like turning around behind the island and like sprinkle it around so that every dragonette can eat this like fish barbecue.
David S. Kong: So you're imagining the statue making…
Tim Sackton: Taking its hand, reaching down into the ocean, scooping up a bunch of fish.
David S. Kong: Okay, okay.
Tim Sackton: holding it out in front of its face, using its presumed, Heska assumes it must have laser eyes, using its laser eyes to cook.
Tim Sackton: Like cook, like cook the fish, like just sear them lightly, and then like turning around and dropping the fish over the island.
David S. Kong: Make an insight check.
Tim Sackton: That's at 12.
David S. Kong: And you're like deeply like imagining this scene?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Okay, cool. I'm going to tell you what happens in a second. Tony, what are you doing?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So I'm sitting back in the chair and kind of closing my eyes and like just soaking it all in and soaking up the vibes. And then I'm also like, as my mind is wandering, you know, it's been.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's been, like, 10 minutes since
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Glenda, my seagull familiar, got here and, like, the charm is starting to wear off and I'm
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I'm thinking about, like, are there other seagulls I've met recently who I think might be, like, a good match or someone I could introduce her to for, like, a more healthy relationship?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): So I'm… I'm sort of, like… and then I sort of get on, like, this imagination of, like, what is a seagull wedding like, and, like, when two little birds, like, fly along, so that's…
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like a healthy relationship for Glenda is sort of where my head is as I'm absentmindedly looking around.
David S. Kong: Sculpt it, what are you doing?
Mike Sackton: Sculpets, is this… Sculpet's thinking about the palm. Does this, like, have any of the same vibe as the Wanderer's palm?
David S. Kong: On.
David S. Kong: Like, yeah, I mean, vibe, sure. I mean, you're inside the wanderer, you know what I mean?
Mike Sackton: instance.
David S. Kong: It's not it's this is yeah. I mean, it's not like, you know, it's not like this is, like, cold. I mean, it's fucking weird in here. Like, it's Yeah.
Mike Sackton: there!
David S. Kong: But but it's not like.
David S. Kong: Yeah, like, the aesthetic… there's definitely, like… It's not right.
Mike Sackton: It's more like he's trying to find, like, the same kind of… peace, and like…
David S. Kong: Mmm.
Mike Sackton: good feeling.
David S. Kong: Oh, you got that. Yeah.
Mike Sackton: It's sort of imagining that.
David S. Kong: You definitely have. I mean, again, this chair, if you heard my description of the chair, this chair is the chair, you know what I mean? You're definitely, like, in a nap, like, very, like.
David S. Kong: Very, very much, you know, so it's just…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: This is…
Mike Sackton: And he's mostly just kind of…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Thinking about the, kind of, connection between different places and…
Mike Sackton: He's a little, I mean, he has, he has like these moments of curiosity where he thinks like look around and be like.
Mike Sackton: What the hell is this place? I should probably figure it out. Lily's kind of like…
Mike Sackton: But, you know, like, should I really, like, you know, it's like, I mean, there's this vibe and then he kind of thinks about the, and then he thinks about the, the palm and like the coziness of being there and like.
Mike Sackton: Kinda daydreams for a few minutes, then he's, like, starts to look again at some, like, the next thing, interesting thing.
Mike Sackton: And then it kind of stops again.
David S. Kong: All right, so as all of you are doing this, Heska, you are the one that's imagining the statue doing something.
David S. Kong: And as you're focusing on this image of the Wanderer actually like moving and reaching down and using its palm and picking up fish and then shooting laser beams out of its eyes, that's the other thing you imagined?
Tim Sackton: Yep.
Eric Rosenbaum: It's.
David S. Kong: And the rest of you are, you know, you're lost in your thoughts, kind of sleeping and feeling those moments of peace.
David S. Kong: Unmistakably, you start feeling the whole room start to shudder and you start to feel that.
David S. Kong: This humming noise that you had heard before, the frequency is picking up.
David S. Kong: And definitely something is happening. There's like a shaking and a creaking of like.
David S. Kong: Sounds and machines and, you know, kind of objects that have not creaked in who knows how long.
David S. Kong: There are 8 seats that are part of this area, and even though you're sitting at the 4 that call to you.
David S. Kong: You notice lights starting to kind of flicker on and off energy around these other seats as well. And you see just kind of a flickering of energy and activation throughout the whole space as everything is starting to shudder and it feels like something is creaking on.
David S. Kong: Heska, are you… what do you do, Heska?
Tim Sackton: I'm like, let's walk to the storm!
David S. Kong: Is that what you start thinking?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Is everybody else still… anybody else doing anything in reaction to this.
David S. Kong: What's happening in the room now?
Eric Rosenbaum: I think Zeno's starting to wake up. Likes the walk to the storm idea.
Eric Rosenbaum: Hyping it up.
David S. Kong: Wait, Heska, do you say that like out loud in your mind or are you just thinking that to yourself?
Tim Sackton: I think I'm thinking it to myself, but also not… remembering about.
David S. Kong: The.
Tim Sackton: Tony's telepathy, so actually thinking it to everybody.
David S. Kong: Alright, so everybody now gets this walk to the island message.
David S. Kong: Walk to the,
Mike Sackton: I don't… Don't think we should leave the island.
David S. Kong: I.
Eric Rosenbaum: I mean, we can.
Tim Sackton: Too late! Get on the train!
Eric Rosenbaum: ocean.
Mike Sackton: I think so.
Eric Rosenbaum: all.
Mike Sackton: Wait, wait, no, this is a place of calmness, peace.
Mike Sackton: Right? I'll think very calming thoughts to the statue, like, like, we're here to… to observe…
Tim Sackton: Walk past.
Mike Sackton: day.
Tim Sackton: Warm!
Eric Rosenbaum: Wanderer's gonna wander.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, come on.
Eric Rosenbaum: it'll be.
Mike Sackton: We don't want to watch.
David S. Kong: Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, okay, wait. So we've got, we've got, Sculpit advocating peace. We now have, Zeno on board with walking. Tony, what's going on for you in this situation? What is, what is your, what is your vibe here?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): What is my vibe here?
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): I think Tony just wants to go, like, take an amble, like, he doesn't have, like, a direction he wants to go to, as much as, like, let's… let's go in knee-deep.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Like, maybe let's go for a swim, actually. Like, I don't wanna…
Tim Sackton: Yes.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): we.
Tim Sackton: A swim would be awesome!
Mike Sackton: I mean, get us killed!
David S. Kong: Okay, with 3 of you now thinking about the statue, 3 of you now are thinking about the statue actually going for a swim, is that the, is that the consensus?
Tim Sackton: Well, at least walking knee-deep into the water.
David S. Kong: Okay.
David S. Kong: With 3 out of 4 of you and 3 out of 8 of these seats.
David S. Kong: Now, fully on board with this, we are gonna go and swim image.
David S. Kong: Unmistakably, and Zeno, you feel this in particular.
David S. Kong: this whole system is humming now. There are frequencies coming alive, sounds that have just…
David S. Kong: You don't really know the word machine, but it's like there's machinery that is afoot, moving, lights, energy coursing and pulsing through this whole space.
David S. Kong: And… As the 3 of you are thinking together about
David S. Kong: The statue standing and moving and going and swimming.
David S. Kong: All of the lights in this entire space.
David S. Kong: Start raising intensity and the whole room and the entire space is now bright, bright, bright.
David S. Kong: And… As we zoom out, And kind of trace up the mechanical shaft.
David S. Kong: Both of the wanderer's eyes now.
David S. Kong: Wide open and shining a blue, bright, bright light, much like the statues below.
David S. Kong: And a light courses throughout the entire Wanderer.
David S. Kong: Through unknown cracks and seams that felt like they were stone now are illuminated.
David S. Kong: And the Wanderer itself, You can feel it.
David S. Kong: Now that you're in the heartbeat, you're in the heart.
David S. Kong: It almost feels as though the whole room is pulsing.
David S. Kong: And it almost feels as though.
David S. Kong: There's a heart that's actually beating inside the statue, and that you are inside that heart, and that you're feeling this deep, deep pulse.
David S. Kong: And the dragonettes on the outside of the Wanderer are like, holy shit. I mean, this is the craziest 24 hours anybody has ever experienced. Jubilee was crazy, but then the food starts appearing, the roads are lighting up, and now the fucking statues, the eyes are… But this, what's happening with the Wanderer, everyone on the island can see it from across.
David S. Kong: This whole shimmering energy and this feeling of this pulsing sensation.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: throughout The Wanderer.
David S. Kong: And the entire island is stunned. Every single dragonet, Tony, all of the objects that are, you know, normally clattering and chatting.
David S. Kong: are all in awe looking up at this scene of the Wanderer, now fully glowing, these seams and these patterns part of this massive statue that has just been stone for as long as anybody can remember.
David S. Kong: And as everybody is in awe, Looking at this scene, I'm looking at this incredible
David S. Kong: Awakening. That's the only way to describe it. And this beating heart of this massive, massive statue staring outwards.
David S. Kong: We… Zoom out from the island.
David S. Kong: And… Start looking out and again at this pulsing statue, seemingly awakening after a long, long slumber.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And we zoom out.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: through… The endless storm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The endless sea leading into the endless storm.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That surrounds the island.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And we passed through the storm.
David S. Kong: And there's so much strange electricity and…
Audio shared by David S. Kong: magic. No dragonet has ever passed through the storm. Nobody ever does.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Sign up to school.
David S. Kong: And the.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The storm is thick, and it's… Dangerous.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: It has a very, very frightening energy. Go away. That's what the energy of the storm says. Go away.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: But as we pass through the storm, and outside to the periphery of the storm, There's something there.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: There's a vessel.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hovering in the sky.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And inside the vessel, We zoom in, and you can see two figures inside a room.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Inside this vessel, hovering in the sky on the outskirts.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Of the storm.
David S. Kong: And there's two humanoids.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: it's there.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: standing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And they're standing around some type of device, or artifact.
David S. Kong: system.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: with.
David S. Kong: Glowing psychedelic lights.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: just.
David S. Kong: tracing these crazy.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: I mean, it's just bouncing everywhere, these light signatures.
David S. Kong: and.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And as we look at this scene, Of these two humanoids.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You zoom in now just to hear some of their voices in their conversation.
David S. Kong: and.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: As they stand over this artifact, these glowing lights.
David S. Kong: moving, shifting in the pattern.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: here Two voices, communicating back and forth, one says.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: This is impossible.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: How is this possible that we're seeing.
David S. Kong: these.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: energy signatures.
David S. Kong: One of them, you can tell, is emotional.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Like, in tears.
David S. Kong: We've been searching.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: for so long.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: How is it possible?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: That we could…
David S. Kong: find.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: See divine energy like this.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: This is impossible.
David S. Kong: the.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Do you know what this means?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: What this is gonna mean for the resistance?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: This is gonna change everything.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: And look… And they say, these signatures, there's something special about them.
David S. Kong: whole.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: is.
David S. Kong: crazy.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Four signatures here, in particular, Unmistakable.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: impossible.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: How is this possible?
David S. Kong: It's gonna only mean.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Hey.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: firstborn.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: The music's a tiny bit loud.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Maybe that's on purpose.
Eric Rosenbaum: Edmonton.
Mike Sackton: This is all set up well, should I say what I think this is?
Audio shared by David S. Kong: You can hold what you, you can hold it if you want.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Or you can say whatever you want. Hold on, hold on, let me… I'm gonna share one more thing.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Okay.
Audio shared by David S. Kong: Oh, no. That's what I meant. That's annoying.
David S. Kong: Well, that's it, guys.
Tim Sackton: Awesome.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, we're on for… Monday the 5th, for the final session.
David S. Kong: Let me see… Is that when we're doing this next?
Tim Sackton: That's what we scheduled last time.
David S. Kong: I thought it was… yeah, yeah, that works. Yeah, that actually works. I fly to California on Tuesday, so we'll wrap this up next time.
Eric Rosenbaum: Nice.
David S. Kong: I do want to share one thing, hold on.
David S. Kong: Yes, I think.
David S. Kong: And speed wraps.
David S. Kong: Goodbye.
David S. Kong: Cool.
David S. Kong: Okay, here it is.
David S. Kong: Hold on.
David S. Kong: Just give me one second here.
David S. Kong: Did anybody catch,
David S. Kong: Does anybody did anybody catch this this Easter egg of like what we're looking at here.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yes.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Absolutely.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Looking at a brain scan.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, it works like.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): From Akira.
Mike Sackton: Saturday.
David S. Kong: What's that?
Tim Sackton: It looks like what?
Mike Sackton: I was gonna say it looks like the Crown of Purity, but that's not what it really is. What is it? It's an Easter egg from some anime.
David S. Kong: Hold on.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It's a permit.
Eric Rosenbaum: Very familiar.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: What's that?
Mike Sackton: Oh, Akira.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): Yeah, from a kid.
David S. Kong: Yeah, from Akira.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): It needs a poorly dubbed voice in the background going like, but that's impossible. That can't be happening.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
Mike Sackton: Yeah, wow.
Eric Rosenbaum: That's fine.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That was super fun, y'all.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: See everybody.
Eric Rosenbaum: select.
David S. Kong: Alright, just really quick before we go. I actually am very curious, like, just very quickly, what you think is happening.
Mike Sackton: business.
Tim Sackton: Don't start with that.
David S. Kong: That's it? That does start with… okay, alright, alright. Well, let's not start with Mike, then. We'll… we can…
Mike Sackton: I'm sorry, I hope… I don't know if anybody heard me, but I won't…
David S. Kong: You can privately message me what you think is going on, for fun, and then, well, we can.
Mike Sackton: 5.
David S. Kong: today.
David S. Kong: Till the next time.
Eric Rosenbaum: Cool.
David S. Kong: Hold on, let me, how do I stop sharing screen? Let's see… Oh, how do I?
David S. Kong: Oh, I can leave immersive view. Alright, cool.
David S. Kong: Guys, immersive backgrounds, it's the way.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
Eric Rosenbaum: It is.
Mike Sackton: Yeah.
Mike Sackton: Very cool.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): When we're the success.
Mike Sackton: Yes.
Tim Sackton: Okay.
Tim Sackton: I…
Mike Sackton: I still have to go finish my… Oh, go, go finish.
Mike Sackton: I'm down to, like, pasting in text from our lawyers, so I'm almost done, but…
Tim Sackton: Are you watching the mic?
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mike Sackton: My question for Cox, Eric.
David S. Kong: Do you want to do that one on one?
Mike Sackton: Good night, everybody.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Rev. David Schwartz (he/him): That's it.
David S. Kong: Okay, alright, bye.
Eric Rosenbaum: Yeah, dudes.
David S. Kong: Good night.
Tim Sackton: Just so I don't get the wrong idea, so firstborn… so technically the Wanderer wouldn't be a firstborn.
David S. Kong: No, no.
Tim Sackton: But you know that, right?
David S. Kong: Oh, yeah. Okay. So you met some. But you know what the reference is. He said there's four energy signatures.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
David S. Kong: Yeah, you are the dragonette firstborn.
Tim Sackton: Right.
David S. Kong: Yeah.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I get it. I just was… I just wanted to make sure that…
David S. Kong: Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Tim Sackton: Mike definitely figured it out.
David S. Kong: Figured out what?
Tim Sackton: Mike knows for sure that this is the setup to New Hampshire.
David S. Kong: Got it.
Tim Sackton: Absolutely, 100% for sure.
David S. Kong: That's good. That's good for him. Yeah. Does he, was it when I started talking about the resistance?
Tim Sackton: Yes, it was the minute you said, you know what this means for the resistance, he immediately figured it out.
David S. Kong: Is that, does he know about the fact that there is a resistance in the thing?
Tim Sackton: No, no, no. You could just see it quick in his face. I'm sure that he knows.
David S. Kong: But that's great.
Tim Sackton: Nobody else. Eric and Schwartz definitely don't know.
David S. Kong: No, no, no. But it's good. It's great. I mean, this is, this is the, as long as everybody gets a satisfying reveal, I mean, you knew this in the beginning that this was gonna be the case. So we're, we're, we're, we're, we're, we're moving.
Tim Sackton: You gotta send me those images, and I love the…
Tim Sackton: the last… I assume this was intentional, the last image is in, like, the sort of anime, arcane style.
David S. Kong: Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Tim Sackton: I love it.
David S. Kong: This is the, you know, the… I mean, it's a tight 3-arc session, Tim. Tim, like, I think for me, obviously, this is, like, my only… my only… my second time doing this, like, since probably I was in high school, but I've… at least for myself, I've figured out, kind of, like.
David S. Kong: I wish I had more time, dude, I have so much fucking shit going on, you have no idea. It's like, like, fucking the next, like… it's like MIT Future Fest, I have, like, so much shit, but I was like, fuck it, like, it's like, let's bring it on, let's do all the things, like, I prepared this session over the past, like, 48 hours, just, like, in between, like.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: like, all the But I think, like, what I've realized, like, for me, it's like.
David S. Kong: like, each… I just need, like… like, it's basically each… each session is, like, 5 to 7 scenes.
David S. Kong: each scene, just, like, type, just, like, keep it, keep it moving, and then, like, like, you know, I'll generate an image, just so I also have a sense of, like, what the thing is, and then, and then just, like, you know.
David S. Kong: Yeah, but it's been really fun. I wish I've had, like, more time to, like, be, like, more kind of… because, like, you know, once you start getting in there, you're like, oh, this could be way cooler if this happened and that happened, and then there's kind of, like, a certain level of, like, surface cool, but…
David S. Kong: Yeah. Anyways, man, it's been super fun. It's been very, you know…
Tim Sackton: Yeah, it's been awesome. I mean… I, you know, the…
Tim Sackton: You don't need, like you see, you don't actually need to really know the rules to run a good game.
David S. Kong: Oh, not at all. Not at all. No. Well, and that's the thing, man. It's like, this is what I was trying to say too before. It's like, I'm not really like, it's like the actual d and d, but the dice rolling is fun. Like doing all the.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, exactly.
David S. Kong: Something that's, like, super fun. Right.
David S. Kong: But, but yeah, it's definitely, like, like, you know, it is kind of like DJing, it's like, you have, like, a good structure, but then definitely a lot of stuff is, like, you know, you kind of freestyle it in the moment. Like, I didn't know… I thought the shaman was going to be a more solemn figure, but then once we were there, it's just, like, all the dragonets are just so, like, even the shamanic dragonets are all, like.
David S. Kong: let's start this restaurant, you know what I mean? It's like… it's like, like, there's no… it just kind of felt like, alright, well, this is the energy of the whole thing, which is, like, great, you know what I mean? It's like this cool, you know…
David S. Kong: So I don't know. I think I just it's like that. I think everybody's role playing has been super good, too. It's been like really fun. Just like everybody's been like super like leaning into the Dragonet energy. Yeah.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I really like this character. Like.
Tim Sackton: I don't know, there's something about some character…
Tim Sackton: Like, Charo, I liked Charo, but I never really clicked with Charo. I was always like, what am I actually doing with this character?
Tim Sackton: But there's a good energy to this… this group. I think it's fun to do, like, a…
David S. Kong: Tim, you know, one like DMing thing that I've been doing that's been kind of interesting, because like, obviously, I've got like a narrative arc that I'm trying to get through, you know?
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: overall, like, story. But then, like, the actual, like, things, like, what I'm really doing is, like.
David S. Kong: figuring out what each of your characters is, and just creating shit so that your characters can do cool shit, you know what I mean? So it's, like, it's actually very character-centric. It's sort of, like, thinking about each character and, like, what your… what your thing… like, what you care about and what you want to do, and then constructing
David S. Kong: like, engagements where that character gets to shine and do whatever the their thing is, so it's like, you know what I mean? So it's like, so that every character, at least once per session, is, like, kind of gets to have, like, a moment of, like, I'm, like, doing some cool for my character, you know?
Tim Sackton: That's like, that's classic DMing advice, but it's, I mean, it's…
Tim Sackton: It's good, it's like… it's… it's fun when you pull it off.
David S. Kong: Yeah, I mean, I've definitely felt at times, like.
David S. Kong: like, certain things where it's like… like, I could see how, like, you want to just focus on the story, and just, like, or whatever you're trying to do, and then have the characters, like, inhabit this thing you've created. But I do think there's, like, another, which is just, like.
David S. Kong: like, having the thing designed for the characters, you know what I mean? So that it's gonna be… and so, you know, there's tensions. There's always kind of tensions in how you want to, like, construct the various, like, interactions, but…
David S. Kong: Yeah, no, definitely it's, it's,
David S. Kong: I wish I had, like, a little… I just wish I'd had more time, like, to kind of set these things up a little bit better, but it's been, you know, it's worked out.
Tim Sackton: Yeah, I don't think you need… I mean…
Tim Sackton: You can spend a… you can… you can spend a lot of time.
Tim Sackton: prepping, but…
David S. Kong: Tim, I think it's for me because I don't have like experience. So like, I don't like, this is like literally my second time doing this.
Tim Sackton: Yeah.
David S. Kong: Like, I don't have, like, for me, more preparation would make it feel like, like, more, like, tight in some ways, but.
Tim Sackton: But what I'm saying is, from the other side of the table, it doesn't feel like it's not tight.
David S. Kong: That's great.
Tim Sackton: Right? Like, you… what… this is what I'm trying to say, is, like. as a D… when you're running… as a DM running games, you always feel like you need… like, some of the… like, some of the most fun sessions I've run are things where I was just like, you did something totally unexpected, and I just completely improvised it.
David S. Kong: Yeah, yeah.
Tim Sackton: By the skin of my pants, right? Which, you know, not the easiest thing to do as you're on your second session, right? But like, you don't need…
Tim Sackton: It doesn't…